human and physical communities to switch levels where we can supply foodmouths and vegan foods and overcome hunger need.
人間と物理的なコミュニティは、食口とビーガン食品を供給し、飢餓のニーズを克服できるレベルに切り替える必要があります。
Director Wang Jin-mo plans to present project into the best possible outcome ofana
ワン・ジンモ監督は、プロジェクトを最高の成果に導く計画だ
miss of knowledge in september
9月の知識不足
So today we're talking about the tax system
さて今日は税制の話です
So, I wonder if you have noticed that in July this year
さて、今年の7月に気づいたでしょうか？
Sino-British Institute puts forward a proposal for tax reform
中英研究所が税制改革案を提出
Then this proposal has aroused a very wide discussion
その後、この提案は非常に幅広い議論を引き起こしました
Well there's a lot of detail in it
まあ、そこにはたくさんの詳細があります
no way to report them all here i think
ここですべてを報告する方法はないと思います
this
これ
part of the tax reform proposal
税制改革案の一部
It's already fermenting
もう発酵してるよ
Especially in the sale and purchase of houses, etc.
特に住宅などの売買においては。
You can see this related issue
この関連問題が表示されます
Well, it's already fermenting
いや、もう発酵してるよ
be directly or indirectly affected by it
それによって直接的または間接的に影響を受ける
The main moderator of this proposal is Academician Wang Ping in the United States
この提案の主な司会者は米国の学者、王平氏です。
The person in charge in Taiwan is the specific researcher Peng Xinkun present here.
台湾の責任者は、ここにいる特定の研究者、彭新君です。
he is here this year
彼は今年ここにいます
Well, some of them are also Yang Jiancheng present here.
さて、彼らの中にはヤン・ジャンチェンもここにいます。
identification
特定
already responsible
すでに責任がある
Colleagues feel that Taiwan's tax system
同僚は台湾の税制をこう感じている
There have been quite a few problems with the structure for a long time
構造には長い間かなりの問題がありました
There are also quite a few unfair issues
不公平な問題も多々ある
And the most important thing is that the taxman's lies are too strong
そして最も重要なことは、税務官の嘘が強すぎるということです
make the government unable to have enough power
政府が十分な権力を持てなくなる
to do what should be done public
公にすべきことをする
or aspects of welfare
または福利厚生の側面
The government's administrative tools have also been severely shot
政府の管理ツールも深刻な攻撃を受けている
So it's a very complex and very difficult problem
つまり、これは非常に複雑で非常に難しい問題です
worthy of further discussion
さらに議論する価値がある
Today we invite the Academia Sinica
今日は中央研究院をご招待します。
Special Review Fellow at the Institute of Economics
経済研究所特別審査員
Professor Yang Jiancheng came to give a lecture
楊建成教授が講義に来られました
Professor Yang is a very distinguished economist
ヤン教授は非常に著名な経済学者です
I think anyone here who has a major in economics knows
経済学を専攻している人なら誰でも知っていると思いますが、
he is an excellent economist
彼は優秀な経済学者です
He is in this
彼はこの中にいます
Virginia Politec
バージニアポリテック
It's the school where Koreans shot and killed a lot of people
朝鮮人が多くの人を射殺した学校です
He is Virginia Polytech's 1989
彼はバージニア工科大学の 1989 年です。
PhD
博士号
Then go back to Academia Sinica
それから中央研究院に戻ります
Has been serving the contract
契約を履行してきた
In addition to being a member of the Institute of Economics, Academia Sinica
中央研究院経済研究所の会員であることに加えて、
Outside of Terby Fellows
特畢研究員以外
It is also an official university finance department
大学の正式な財務学部でもあります
Chair Professor
講座教授
His specialty is public economics
彼の専門は公共経済学です
and political economy
そして政治経済
Professor Wan from Academia Sinica
中央研究院のワン教授
From associate researcher to special researcher
准研究員から特別研究員へ
He has received many important academic honors
彼は多くの重要な学術的栄誉を受賞している
Including Ministry of Education Academic Award 1994
1994年度文部大臣学術賞を含む
Including three NSC End Research Awards
3つのNSCエンドリサーチ賞を含む
including the National Science Council's 2002
2002 年の米国科学会議を含む
Extraordinary research awards and more
特別な研究賞など
so he is a
だから彼は
medal-filled economist
メダルいっぱいの経済学者
A topic he is going to talk about today
彼が今日話そうとしている話題
in fact it is important
実際それは重要です
Income tax versus consumption tax
所得税と消費税
So as we prepare this
それで、これを準備するときに、
tax reform
税制改革
time for tax reform proposals
税制改革提案の時期
there is an academician
学者がいます
Fellows in the United States
米国のフェロー
He just thinks
彼はただ考えているだけです
GST should be used as a starting point
GST を開始点として使用する必要があります
Others are of course this opinion is too strong
もちろん他の人もこの意見は強すぎる
Didn't get everyone's credit
全員の信用を得られなかった
So these issues are very complicated
したがって、これらの問題は非常に複雑です
we now use applause
今は拍手を使っています
Welcome Professor Yang Jiancheng to us
楊建成教授をようこそ
Thank you all for coming
お越しいただきありがとうございました
this time the speech
今回のスピーチは
i just mentioned that
私はちょうどそれを言いました
I am Berzene Tech B.Ed
私は Berzene Tech B.Ed です
It was a Korean who killed many people
多くの人を殺害したのは朝鮮人だった
Later my junior college
その後、私の短大
tell me
教えて
because of that
そのための
Make our school more famous
私たちの学校をもっと有名にする
So in the future recruit new students
そこで今後は新入生を募集します
Yellow tuna is more active
キハダマグロは活性が高い
It might not have been that famous
そこまで有名ではなかったかもしれない
for killing a bunch of people
大勢の人を殺したために
So it becomes more famous
それでもっと有名になるんだよ
So everyone is more enthusiastic about yellow tuna
だからみんなキハダマグロにもっと熱中するんだよ
Thank you all for coming
お越しいただきありがとうございました
That is to say, let’s talk about it a little bit wider than this.
つまり、これよりもう少し広い範囲で話しましょう。
But let me talk about an idea about a center
しかし、センターについてのアイデアについて話させてください
So Luo Rui is not a very good Rui in Taiwan
つまり、ルオ・ルイは台湾ではあまり良いルイではないのです。
not very good ray
あまり良くない光線
We'll get to that in a minute but it has a lot of problems
それについてはすぐに説明しますが、多くの問題があります
Well Sorori is not very good Ray
まあソロリはあまり良くないレイ
So is it possible to subsidize or help this Rui with other Rui?
では、このルイに補助金を出したり、他のルイを援助したりすることは可能でしょうか？
It’s probably a central issue that I’m going to talk about today.
おそらくこれが、私が今日話そうとしている中心的な問題です。
I'll probably talk about why Solori isn't that good
ソロリがそれほど良くない理由についてはおそらく話します
Why it is possible to use other ri to help or subsidize the words of sorori
ソロリの言葉を助けるために他のリを使用することができる理由
Maybe we can make our Rui characters better
Ruiのキャラクターをより良くできるかもしれません
What I just said is that what I probably talked about is not just about this
私が今言ったのは、おそらく私が話したのはこのことだけではないということです
I'm probably a little wider
たぶんもう少し幅が広いと思います
I would like to mention some information now
今からいくつかの情報について述べたいと思います
I probably won't say it, you should know
おそらく言わないだろう、知っておくべきだ
It's our debt
それは私たちの借金です
This is where we equal the central
ここが中心に匹敵する場所です
we last time
私たちは前回
It was just mentioned by Wang Wu
それはWang Wuが言及したばかりです
He has this picture in the report
彼は報告書にこの写真を載せています
you can draw that is to say
つまり描くことができます
our words in 81
81年の私たちの言葉
He takes that as the unit
彼はそれを単位として捉えています
Look at the words in 1981
1981年の言葉を見てください
about 0 years 57
約0年 57
In other words, about 0.5 megabytes
つまり約0.5メガバイト
you can draw that is to say
つまり描くことができます
whose time passes
時間が経つ人
You can draw me higher and higher
あなたは私をもっと高く引き寄せることができます
Now it's about 5 trillion
今は5兆くらいです
Some people say this is not very accurate
これはあまり正確ではないと言う人もいます
Because it also includes, for example, some
たとえば、いくつかのものも含まれているため、
old insurance loss catholic
古い保険損失カトリック
future problems
今後の問題
But dare not do anything
でもあえて何もしないで
tell us here
ここで教えてください
You see, this growth rate is quite fast.
ご覧のとおり、この成長速度は非常に速いです。
And you see he is going up
そして彼が上がっていくのがわかります
how about going backwards
後戻りしてはどうでしょうか
We are now roughly every year
今ではほぼ毎年行っています
about every year
ほぼ毎年
The one from 200 billion to 300 billion is equal to
2,000 億から 3,000 億までは次のようになります。
Equal to insufficient tax or other income
不十分な税金またはその他の収入に等しい
In other words, among our expenditures
つまり、私たちの支出の中には、
probably probably
おそらくおそらく
200 to 300 billion
2000億から3000億
It depends on our year
それは私たちの年によって異なります
tax good bad bad
税金良い悪い悪い
don't remember good words
良い言葉を覚えていない
tax is better
税金の方が良い
Remember that when you are poor, your taxes are poor.
あなたが貧しいときは、税金も貧弱であることを忘れないでください。
But probably as short as
しかし、おそらく同じくらい短い
200 to 300 billion
2000億から3000億
The ratio is the same
比率は同じです
If this proportion
この割合なら
That is to say, he is here
つまり、彼はここにいるのです
The average proportion of GDP in terms of the previous three years
過去3年間のGDPに占める割合の平均
you see you know
わかりますね
is also an upward
も上向きです
if you go up
上がれば
You see, it was around 13:00 at the beginning
そうですね、最初は13時くらいでした
Now the word is probably in
今、その言葉はおそらく入っています
in a short period of time
短期間で
Now about 3 times and 4 times more
現在大概3倍4倍多
to 37 o'clock
37時まで
this number
この番号
i think it's ok
大丈夫だと思います
better than the rest of the world
世界の他の地域よりも優れている
But the worry is that this trend
しかし、心配なのは、この傾向が
that trend
その傾向
This trend means
この傾向が意味するのは、
It is equivalent to more than thirty-seven points from a total amount
合計金額から37ポイント以上相当
You are better than other countries in the world
あなたは世界の他の国よりも優れています
Like Japan, it is more than 100%
日本同様100％以上
better than many other countries
他の多くの国よりも優れている
But its rising figures make us more worried
しかし、その数字の上昇が私たちをさらに不安にさせます
we are more worried
私たちはもっと心配です
ok this is what we mean
わかりました、これが私たちが言いたいことです
My tax burden ratio in recent years
近年の私の税負担率
This is also what we have in the report of the Central Committee
これは中央委員会の報告書にもあります。
Probably you can draw until about eleven or twelve
おそらく11時か12時くらいまでは描けるでしょう
Probably since 1991
おそらく1991年以来
this number
この番号
How does it compare to other countries?
他の国と比べてどうですか？
let's take a look
見てみましょう
This is probably how many countries we have
おそらくこれが私たちが持っている国の数です
Take a look like the Republic of China and the United States
中華民国とアメリカのように見てください
What we say in Taiwan is probably like what we just said
台湾で私たちが言っていることは、おそらく私たちが今言ったことと同じです
Since 1991, it has been around eleven o'clock
1991年以来、それは11時頃です
In the past it was higher
昔はもっと高かったのに
It's after fifteen o'clock
十五時過ぎです
You can see and go down slowly
ゆっくりと下っていくことができます
go down slowly
ゆっくりと下ります
It includes A and B
AとBが含まれます
A and B
A跟B
Because if it's past 12 o'clock
12時を過ぎると
That doesn't include us, for example, paying some annuities
たとえば、年金の支払いなどは含まれません。
paid some health insurance fees
健康保険料の一部を支払った
because other countries
なぜなら他の国は
Annuity payments are basically part of a tax
年金の支払いは基本的に税金の一部です
the annuity you pay the health insurance you pay
あなたが支払う年金 あなたが支払う健康保険
basically
基本上
But let's split it into two columns
ただし、2 つの列に分割しましょう
As far as column A is concerned
A列に関する限り
Just doesn't include social security contributions
これには社会保険料は含まれません
including not including annuity
年金を含めない
health insurance not included
健康保険は含まれていません
This V course includes
この自然な単語には次のものが含まれます
If you look at the comparison
比較してみると
Even if we look at it with Vran
ヴランで見ても
Compared with other countries
他国と比較して
like in Japan, to the twenties
日本のように20代まで
Thirty in German
ドイツ語で「30」
words of anglicization
英語化の言葉
Anyway, you talk to France to more than ten
とにかく、あなたはフランスと10人以上に話します
Nordic countries
北欧諸国
are full height
フルハイトです
Now I think Taiwan has a big problem
今、台湾は大きな問題を抱えていると思う
That is to say, the people have quite high unreasonable demands on society.
つまり国民は社会に対してかなり高い理不尽な要求を持っているのです。
I hope the government will provide a lot of social welfare
政府がたくさんの社会福祉を提供してくれることを願っています
But it's hard on angle tax
でも角税は厳しいよ
This is not unreasonable
これは不合理ではありません
not without reason
理由がないわけではない
This is equivalent to the problem of a single machine
これは単一のマシンの問題に相当します
For example, if you talk about Taiwan Telecom
たとえば、台湾電信について言えば、
you want to raise your electricity price
電気料金を値上げしたいと考えています
In the case of CNPC, if the oil price is raised
CNPCが原油価格を引き上げると
It is often said that
よく言われるのは、
you put some of your internal
あなたは自分の内面の一部を注ぎます
Fluctuating line draft without calculation
計算なしで変動する線ドラフト
Let’s fix the problem of the single machine first.
まず単一マシンの問題を解決しましょう。
This is not so clear anymore
これはもうあまり明確ではありません
But if we are comparing
しかし比較してみると
Probably except for comparisons like Singapore
おそらくシンガポールのような比較を除いて
is special like city-state outside
外は都市国家のように特別です
Probably much lower
おそらくもっと低いでしょう
you can take a look
見てみることができます
That is to say, it is not very high
つまりそこまで高くない
but then again
でもまたまた
Although this proportion is not very high
この割合はそれほど高くありませんが、
But who will bear the burden?
しかし、誰がその負担を負うのでしょうか？
I don't think this is as low as I thought.
思ったほど低くないと思います。
We know that Taiwan's
私たちは台湾のことを知っています
If there is a sleeping system, you should be small, including sleeping.
睡眠系があるなら睡眠も含めて小さいほうがいいです。
including sleeping when reporting to sleep
睡眠報告時の睡眠を含む
you just go online
あなたはただオンラインに行くだけです
For example, your buckle feet are flat
たとえば、バックルの足が平らになっているとします。
when you report to sleep
それはあなたが眠りに就くときのようなものです
He will automatically tell you how many hands you have
彼はあなたが持っている手の数を自動的に言います
where did those hands come from
その手はどこから来たのですか
They all come with a single buckle.
すべて単一のバックルが付いています。
Is it flattened?
平らになっていますか？
there is a ser party
サーパーティーがあります
there is a third person in english
英語には第三者がいます
you work for a certain company
あなたは特定の会社に勤めています
when the company pays you for water first
会社が最初に水代を支払うとき
He just pays you the first part of the water
彼は水の最初の部分だけをあなたに支払います
report him to, say, the IRS
彼を例えばIRSに報告する
The IRS has that information.
IRS はその情報を持っています。
let's wait and see
待って見ましょう
Taiwan has a structural problem
台湾は構造的な問題を抱えている
That is, there are many small and medium-sized enterprises in Taiwan.
それは、台湾には中小企業がたくさんあるということです。
SMEs this thing
中小企業はこんなこと
It's like being your own boss
まるで自分の上司になったかのような
The function of this ser party is not lost
このサーバーの機能は失われません
otherwise it means
そうでなければそれは意味します
To be able to hold your hand
手を握ることができるように
Why can I get
なぜ入手できるのか
just through this ser party
このパーティーを通じて
just define
ただ定義するだけ
When you pay your salary in that company
その会社で給料を支払うとき
He reported this information to the Ministry of Finance.
彼はその情報を財務省に報告した。
or when the company pays you a bonus
または会社がボーナスを支払ったとき
They know that a lot of people don't have this social party
彼らは、多くの人がこのような社交パーティーに参加していないことを知っています
For example, Sale Impointment
たとえば、販売のインポイントメント
Now that you're the boss, he won't have this social party
あなたが上司になった今、彼はこの社交パーティーを開催しません
So this probably won't go away.
したがって、これはおそらく消えないでしょう。
So you see that the tax rate seems to be very high
そうすると税率が非常に高いことがわかります
But it is believed that most
しかし、ほとんどの場合、
Most of it is due to the exchange of salary
そのほとんどは給与の交換によるものです
So this is not very high
なので、これはそれほど高くはありません
But if you count it on the payroll
しかし、それを給与計算に含めると、
Maybe not as low as imagined
想像ほど低くないかもしれない
not as low as imagined
想像ほど低くない
This is also a big problem
これも大きな問題です
Then let's see
それでは見てみましょう
That is to say, this is one of the pictures just now. Take a look.
つまり、これは今の写真の 1 枚です。見てください。
Basically you can draw to get us is very low
基本的に私たちを獲得するために引くことができるのは非常に低いです
In other words the size of our government
言い換えれば、私たちの政府の規模
Compared with other countries, it is very low.
他国と比べても非常に低いです。
very low
とても低い
Yes Japan
有日本
look and compare
見て比較してください
like danish words
デンマーク語の言葉のように
denmark like nordic countries words
デンマークのような北欧の言葉
at 50 is really over 50
50歳は本当に50歳を超えている
This is normal in the West
西洋ではこれが普通だ
So their social welfare is doing well
彼らは社会福祉において良い仕事をしている
not without reason
理由がないわけではない
because in your hand
なぜならあなたの手の中に
most are taxed
ほとんどが課税される
pay taxes
税金を払う
But Taiwan's problem is
しかし台湾の問題は
pay little tax
わずかな税金を支払う
but hope that the government will provide high welfare
しかし、政府が高福祉を提供してくれることを願っています
This gap creates a big problem
このギャップが大きな問題を引き起こす
OK
OK
this is
これは
Of course, Taiwan now has another problem, that is,
もちろん、台湾は現在別の問題を抱えています。
equal to
に等しい
A problem of uneven distribution
偏在の問題
This is of course from before
これはもちろん以前から
You see what it says here
ここに書いてあることがわかります
The board with the highest hand and the back of the board with the lowest
最も高いハンドを持つボードと最も低いボードのバック
on the rise
上昇傾向に
this rise
この上昇
of course you can draw
もちろん描くこともできます
somewhat likely to be exaggerated
多少誇張されている可能性が高い
a bit exaggerated
少し誇張された
The main reason is that you can draw
一番の理由は絵が描けるからです
in the early days
初めの頃
that population
その人口
It is not the same as the later population structure
後の人口構成と同じではない
For example, in the early days, it may have been a relatively large family.
たとえば、初期の頃は比較的大家族だったかもしれません。
Smaller family now
現在比較小家庭的
Everyone wants to say that my hands are already taller.
誰もが私の手はすでに高くなったと言いたいのです。
so this may be an exaggeration
だからこれは誇張かもしれない
But the main problem is that
しかし、主な問題はそれです
You can see that the trend is indeed going up
確かに上昇傾向にあることがわかります
However, the upward trend
ただし、上昇傾向
It's not a phenomenon of Taiwan retreating
台湾が後退する現象ではない
This phenomenon occurs in many countries around the world
この現象は世界中の多くの国で発生しています
Let's look at the picture below
下の写真を見てみましょう
This picture is also interesting
この写真も面白いですね
It is in the information of your Doctrine
それはあなたの教義の情報の中にあります
Among the materials of the Doctrine of Doctrine
教義の教義の資料の中には
It puts equal to a lock among
ロックに等しいものを置きます
It is mainly divided into two parts
大きく2つのパートに分かれています
part of what we see here
ここで見られるものの一部
remuneration for bereavement
死別に対する報酬
The general salary is the salary for the deceased
一般的な給与は亡くなった人の給与です
normal salary
通常の給与
There are other locks
他にもロックあります
Other locks include profits earned by the company
その他のロックには会社が得た利益が含まれます
and interest
そして興味
Anyway, other locks
とにかく他のロック
ground rent etc.
地代など
This is collectively called operating surplus
これを総称して営業余剰といいます
Anyway, let's say these two together
とにかく、この2つを一緒に言ってみましょう
is what we get
それが私たちが得るものです
Anyway, besides sleeping
とにかく寝る以外にも
probably these two
おそらくこの二人
In addition to sleeping and the so-called depreciation
睡眠といわゆる減価償却に加えて
It's probably mainly these two.
おそらく主にこの２つでしょう。
hand
手的
You got these two
この 2 つを手に入れました
not these two
この二人ではない
Let's say these two have a trend
この2つに傾向があるとしましょう
what trend
どのような傾向ですか
You see this social staff pay
このソーシャルスタッフが給料を払っているのがわかります
Around the time of the 19th year
19年くらいの頃
1989 reached a petition
1989年に請願に達した
But then you see the whole trend and go down
しかしその後、全体の傾向が見えて、下降していきます
what does this mean
これは何を意味するのでしょうか
This means that
この意味は
economic growth
経済成長
For example, economic growth
例えば、経済成長
we are growing
私たちは成長しています
belonging to labor income
労働所得に属する
part of salary
給料の一部
it is getting less and less
それはますます少なくなってきています
Fewer and fewer
ますます少なく
in other words
言い換えると
For example, it is equivalent to earning 100 yuan
例えば、100元の収入に相当します。
for 100 pieces
100個用
you see at this time
この時点でわかりますか
it takes half
半分かかります
right
右
about 50
約50
accounted for half
半分を占めた
right
右
but then what
でもそれではどうする
a coat is falling
コートが落ちている
On the other hand, this is rising
一方で、こちらは上昇中
This phenomenon is not unique to Taiwan.
この現象は台湾に限ったものではありません。
phenomenon in many countries
多くの国で起きている現象
So I saw this case earlier
それで、私はこの事件を以前に見ました
Seeing equals the rising gap is getting bigger and bigger
見ることはイコール、格差はますます大きくなる
about is to say
については言うことです
For example, economic growth
例えば、経済成長
say 3%
3%と言う
or 5%
または5%
Many people say that the five senses
多くの人は五感だと言います。
because of the money
お金のせいで
My salary didn't increase either
給料も上がらなかった
Where will those 5% and 3% growth go?
この 5% と 3% の成長はどこへ行くのでしょうか?
In other words not universally enjoyed
言い換えれば、普遍的に楽しんでいない
You can see that the early days of Taiwan were not like this
台湾の初期はそうではなかったことがわかります
Early Taiwan
初期の台湾
In the early stage of Taiwan, there were many opportunities at that time
台湾の初期段階では、当時は多くのチャンスがありました
Almost I'm as small as among my peers
私は他の仲間とほぼ同じくらい小さいです
as long as high school
高校までは
don't even go to college
大学にも行かないでください
At that time everyone earned college
当時は誰もが大学を稼いだ
At that time there were many chances
あの時はチャンスが多かった
as long as you work hard
あなたが一生懸命働く限り
not that kind
そんな種類ではない
Let's just say how it is
それがどうなっているか言ってみましょう
In other words you just
言い換えれば、あなたはただ
about that time
その頃
equal to many chances
多くのチャンスに等しい
everyone earns college
誰もが大学を稼いでいます
good
良い
we learned to read very high
私たちは非常に高いレベルで読むことを学びました
Doesn't necessarily make more money
必ずしもお金が増えるわけではない
But then we heard
しかしその後、私たちは聞きました
What fat cat is not a fat cat question
デブ猫がデブ猫ではないのはどのような質問ですか
But now you can come back to the whole standstill
でも今は完全な停止状態に戻ることができる
there is this phenomenon
この現象があります
This phenomenon is tantamount to saying that
この現象は、こう言っているのと同じです。
I didn't earn the money
私はお金を稼げませんでした
he made money
彼はお金を儲けた
This phenomenon is also
この現象も、
We see these two phenomena
この 2 つの現象が見られます
actually a
実際には
But it's right that Taiwan has its own problems.
しかし台湾特有の問題は正しい
Don't talk about unique problems
特有の問題について話さない
why is it like this
なぜこんなことになっているのか
As you can imagine there are of course many factors behind this
ご想像のとおり、これにはもちろん多くの要因があります
But probably globalization is probably
しかし、おそらくグローバリゼーションはおそらく
presumably a factor of a running jump
おそらくランニングジャンプの要因
globalization
グローバリゼーション
Because labor is more expensive in your place
あなたのところでは人件費が高くなるから
I won't set up a factory in your place
私はあなたの代わりに工場を設立しません
I went to other places to set up factories
工場を設立するために他の場所に行きました
But there are many factors behind
しかし、その背後には多くの要因があります
But there is this phenomenon
でもこんな現象あるんですね
How to overcome this phenomenon
この現象を克服する方法
How to deal with it
対処方法
This is also a pretty big problem
これもかなり大きな問題です
pretty big problem
かなり大きな問題
Yes, and I want to make a special point about the previous one
はい、特にこれについて話したいと思います
That is to say, among the income of the Taiwan government
つまり、台湾政府の収入のうち、
Taiwan's government revenue is about 2 trillion a year
台湾の政府歳入は年間約2兆円
2 trillion, other than 2 trillion including taxes
2兆、2兆以外は税込み
Ladies and gentlemen, what is the contribution of the central bank among the two trillion?
皆さん、2兆のうち中央銀行の貢献は何ですか？
You may never have thought that contributing is tithe
寄付が十分の一税であるとは考えたこともなかったかもしれません
In other words, two balls are the central bank's surplus
言い換えれば、ボール2個は中央銀行の余剰である
So if you think about it, we generally imagine that the central bank is the monetary policy
考えてみると、私たちは一般に中央銀行が金融政策であると想像します。
It is to control the exchange rate interest rate those policies
為替金利をコントロールする政策です
But the central bank has now become a tax unit that seems to be quite important
しかし、中央銀行は現在、非常に重要な税単位となっているようです
This is the unit that collects money
これはお金を集めるユニットです
Because out of a hundred dollars, out of a hundred dollars spent by the entire government
なぜなら、100ドルのうち、政府全体が費やした100ドルのうちから
Ten out of one hundred yuan of income is from the central bank
収入100元のうち10元は中央銀行からのもの
200 billion is the contribution of the central bank
2000億は中央銀行の拠出額です
If you think about it, this one is very special
考えてみれば、これはとても特別なことだ
It is a very special phenomenon in the world
世界的に見ても非常に特殊な現象です
But Yang Yangyang said, he would say
しかし、ヤン・ヤンヤンはこう言いました。
I have a lot of foreign exchange reserves, and my base is very good
外貨準備がたくさんあり、基盤は非常に良好です
But from the point of view of monetary scholars
しかし貨幣学者の観点から見ると
that is also a tax
それも税金です
Why?
なぜ？
If Yang Yangyang wants to make that money
ヤン・ヤンヤンがその金を稼ぎたいなら
He is bound to drive down interest rates
彼は金利を引き下げるに違いない
This is like a dispute
これは争いみたいなものだ
there is an argument
議論があります
But look, this is not a long-term occasion
しかし、ほら、これは長期的な機会ではありません
You see, Yang Yangyang contributed one of ten papers, 200 billion
ヤン・ヤンヤンは10の論文のうちの1つを寄稿しました、2000億
Among the two trillion, two hundred billion is Yang Xing
二兆二千億の中には楊興もいる
this is very special
これはとても特別なことです
This can't be long
これは長くはなりません
So if you take away Yang Yangyang's share
だからヤンヤンヤンの分を奪ったら
that deficit is worse
その赤字のほうがひどい
As I just said, the annual deficit is about 200 billion to 300 billion
今言ったように、年間の赤字は約2,000億から3,000億です。
If you take Yang Yangyang away
ヤンヤンヤンを奪ったら
Probably suddenly increased to 400 billion, 500 billion
おそらく突然4000億、5000億に増えたでしょう
And this is really, I think it's a pretty serious problem.
そして、これは本当に、かなり深刻な問題だと思います。
Because Yang Yangyang has such a big burden
ヤンヤンヤンには大きな負担があるから
you can tell
教えてもいいよ
I guess and intuit it too
私もそれを直感しています
That is to say, he may interfere with one of his monetary policies
つまり、彼は金融政策のいずれかに干渉する可能性がある。
yes, should have, for example should have done
はい、すべきでした、たとえば、すべきでした
But considering that if you do this, it won't work out.
しかし、これをやるとうまくいかないことを考えると。
I have less money or something
お金が減ったのか何か
he will be restricted
彼は制限されるだろう
So this is not a long time
だから、これは長い時間ではない
But I want POINOUT to point it out
でも POINOUT に指摘してもらいたい
The number of times in Taiwan is quite serious.
台湾の回数はかなり深刻です。
Because the central bank contributed 200 billion
中央銀行が2000億ドルを拠出したため
If you remove the part of the central bank
中央銀行の部分を取り除くと
The number of times per year is 4
年間回数は4回です
Equal to this difference becomes
この差に等しいのは、
Not 200 billion, hundreds of billions
2,000億ではなく、数千億
Become 2000 equal to 400 billion to 500 billion
2000年になると4000億から5000億になる
so it looks serious
だから真剣そうに見える
serious
深刻
Well by this I mean a simple one
まあ、これは単純なことを意味します
Of course there is a feeling
もちろん気持ちはあります
that feeling means
その気持ちが意味するのは
For example, we follow
たとえば、次のようになります。
One that produces a compilation of different faculties
さまざまな学部の編集物を作成するもの
The finances of our Republic of China
中華民国の財政
look at it
それを見てください
Probably tax accounted for more than 73.0
おそらく税金が73.0以上を占めている
india also india
インドもインド
it's serious
それは深刻です
I just said it's past twelve o'clock
さっき12時過ぎって言ったんだけど
The central bank contributes 10%
中央銀行は10％を拠出
Contribute 10%
10％貢献
It means that the central bank is the most profitable state-owned institution
それは中央銀行が最も収益性の高い国有機関であることを意味する
it's really special
それは本当に特別です
maybe i thought maybe in
たぶん私はおそらく入っていると思った
It's also a surprise that I'm knowing
私が知っているのも驚きです
Surprised to know
知って驚いた
It's hard for ordinary people to imagine
普通の人には想像しにくい
The central bank turned out to be the most profitable business unit
中央銀行が最も収益性の高い事業部門であることが判明
But the damage that this says is that
しかし、これが言うダメージは、
A tax on locks is probably in favor
ロックへの課税はおそらく賛成です
Business tax praise so much
事業税はとても賞賛されています
These 30 years add up to about half
この30年は半分くらい
But what I just said at the beginning is to say
しかし、私が冒頭で言いましたのは、
The destruction I'm going to talk about today is the tax on locks
今日私が話そうとしている破壊とは、錠前にかかる税金のことです
not as good as we thought
私たちが思ったほど良くない
let's take a look
見てみましょう
The tax of the lock is theoretically an ideal tax word
理論的には、ロックの税金は理想的な税金の言葉です
Why is it an ideal tax word?
なぜこれが理想的な税用語なのでしょうか?
because it can vary depending on the taxpayer's situation
納税者の状況によって変動する可能性があるため、
deliberately different persuasion
意図的に異なる説得
For example, your home
たとえば、あなたの家
do you have children
子どもはいますか
Is there a major disaster every year
大きな災害は毎年ありますか
So or any sick medical expenses
それで、病気の医療費も
particularly high
特別高
We have a so-called special deduction
いわゆる特別控除があります
Not a special deduction
特別控除ではない
You can deduct it immediately
すぐに引き落とせるよ
Because it depends on your persuasion how many people to support
何人を支持するかはあなたの説得次第だから
how is your condition
体調はどうですか
So it can move forward according to different people
だから、いろんな人に合わせて前に進むことができる
I tax it differently
別の方法で課税します
This tax is theoretically called a direct tax
この税は理論的には直接税と呼ばれます
direct tax
直接税
because according to your condition
なぜならあなたの状況に応じて
I design my tax system
私は税制を設計します
If there is a tax, we villains generally can't scold
税金があれば、私たち悪人は基本的に叱ることはできません
For example, if you go to buy a
たとえば、何かを買いに行くとすると、
For example, LV bags
例えばLVのバッグなど
you like to buy
あなたは買うのが好きですか
Buy LV bags from a rich man
金持ちからLVのバッグを買う
It won't say LV bags this guy is rich
LVバッグこの男が金持ちだなんて言うつもりはない
this guy has no money
この人はお金がない
Maybe there is someone who likes LV bags very much
もしかしたらLVのバッグがすごく好きな人もいるかもしれない
it has no money
それはお金がありません
but it also buys a
しかし、それはまた、
so it can't see
だからそれは見えない
Anyway, it knows when it sees
とにかく、見ればわかる
Only one L88 was sold
L88は1台のみ販売されました
As for who bought it
誰が買ったかというと、
he can't see
彼は見えません
right
右
So what about general sales tax?
では、一般消費税はどうなるのでしょうか？
Generally, only the size of one car can be delivered
基本的に1台分のサイズのみお届け可能です
That is to say, how much are you buying and selling
つまり、いくらで売買しているのかということです
He is not able to adapt to the different circumstances of the taxpayer
彼は納税者のさまざまな状況に適応することができない
I just said that it's like a tax breaker
脱税みたいなものだと言いました
I can see how many children you have
子供が何人いるかわかります
did you raise your parents
あなたは両親を育てましたか
Did you have any major events this year?
今年何か大きなイベントはありましたか？
For example, disaster
たとえば、災害
Are you sick? etc.
病気ですか？など
he can make an adjustment for you
彼はあなたのために調整をしてくれるでしょう
For example, when you enumerate deductions
たとえば、控除を列挙すると、
You can list your medical expenses and so on.
医療費などを一覧表示できます。
So he can according to the situation of different people
だから彼はさまざまな人々の状況に応じて対応できる
different taxation
別の方法で課税される場合があります
But sales tax is gone
でも消費税はなくなった
sales tax anyway
とにかく消費税
you trade
あなたは取引します
The tax of the father who has money to buy you is the same
あなたを買うお金を持っている父親の税金は同じです
all the same
すべて同じ
So generally speaking
一般的に言えば
Different taxes cannot be levied according to different situations of taxpayers
納税者の状況に応じて異なる税金を課すことはできない
indirect tax
間接税
This is called Direct Tax
これを直接税といいます
words in english
英語の言葉
So theoretically
つまり理論的には
in theory
理論上
Hand tax is a better tax
手税の方が良い税金だ
because it can advance according to different
さまざまな状況に応じて進むことができるため、
This measure of customer tax means that
この顧客税の措置は次のことを意味します。
What we traditionally say is
私たちが伝統的に言っていることは、
People with higher income should pay more tax
高所得者はより多くの税金を支払わなければならない
Those who earn less should pay more
収入が少ない人はもっと払うべきだ
less tax etc.
税金などが減ります。
The person with the two heads going forward should pay the tax for the head and so on
今後、二つの頭を持つ人は、頭分の税金を支払わなければなりません。
It can be done differently according to this forward
このフォワードに従って別の方法で実行できます
Just a different design
ただデザインが違うだけ
But sales tax is not
しかし、消費税はそうではありません
No business tax, that is to say
事業税はかからない、つまり
anyway each of you
とにかく皆さんそれぞれ
Yes, you go to a high-end restaurant to eat
はい、高級レストランに食事に行きます
You just have to pay five business taxes
5つの事業税を支払うだけで済みます
It doesn't matter who eats it
誰が食べるかは関係ない
You are buying Taiwanese people to eat, so it is the same
台湾人を買って食べているのだから同じだ
I also pay this tax when I eat today
私も今日食事をするときにこの税金を支払います
yes
はい
So in theory
理論的には
Judgment from the point of view of taxation
課税の観点からの判断
The tax in my hand is the excellent business tax
私の手の税金は立派な事業税です
Merit business tax
メリット事業税
But what I'm going to say next is that
しかし、次に私が言いたいのは、
The tax in hand is not as good as we imagined
手元にある税金は思ったほど良くない
let's take a look
見てみましょう
the information i use
私が使用する情報
The information used below is from 1994
以下に使用されている情報は 1994 年のものです
China's hand tax approved production and trade information
中国の手税承認生産および貿易情報
because my year happened to be
たまたま私の年がそうだったので
make one for the treasury
財務省のために一つ作る
just make a plan
ただ計画を立ててください
But now there is also, now there is a relatively new information
しかし、今はまた、比較的新しい情報があります
But my understanding is not much different, let's take a look at the data of Zengnian
しかし、私の理解はそれほど変わりません。Zengnian のデータを見てみましょう。
Because the number of places reflected in the data, what is it?
データに反映される箇所数が多いので、何だろう？
Let's take a look at the general guardian of the household
世帯の一般後見人について見てみましょう
Those who make friends mean, for example, husband and wife, if we come to see husband and wife
友達を作るというのは、例えば夫婦のことです。私たちが夫婦に会いに来たとしたら、
As long as your total number of defenders reaches 1.3 million, you can use the data of increasing years to see
防御者の総数が 130 万人に達する限り、年々増加するデータを使用して次のことを確認できます。
You are probably dead and rich in the first half of Taiwan
あなたは台湾の前半で死んで金持ちになっているかもしれません
1.3 million, what is it like? Probably every month when you don’t expect to earn
130万、それはどんな感じですか? 収入が期待できない毎月かもしれません
This does not include any deductions
これには控除は含まれません
This gross is equivalent to not deducting anything, for example, how much you have raised children
この総額は、たとえば子供を育てた金額などを何も差し引かないことと同じです。
You're going on vacation and haven't deducted those things yet.
あなたは休暇に行くつもりですが、それらのものをまだ差し引いていません。
In other words, it is right to calculate that you have made money
言い換えれば、「お金を稼いだ」と計算するのが正しいのです。
You see, you only need to earn about 110,000
ほら、11万くらい稼げばいいだけだよ
It's the 10% of rich people
それは10％の富裕層です
in other words
言い換えると
as long as your husband and wife
あなたの夫と妻がいる限り
If it is a public official
公務員であれば
If the husband and wife are both public servants
夫婦とも公務員の場合
on the tax package
税金パッケージについて
You're probably in the 10% rich
あなたはおそらく10％の富裕層に属します
in other words
言い換えると
The couple's money for every other diamond
カップルは 1 つおきにダイヤモンドを費やします
As long as it exceeds 113,000 yuan
113,000元を超える限り
About 10% of rich people
富裕層の約10％
Think about it, everyone
皆さん、考えてみてください
This is the rich man you imagine
これがあなたが想像する金持ちです
I guess there is a gap
ギャップあると思うよ
Both husband and wife are public servants
夫婦とも公務員です
probably rich
おそらく金持ち
when i come
私が来たとき
Our rental laboratory also
弊社レンタルラボもございます
tell me
教えて
Probably your ancestor and wife
おそらくあなたの先祖と妻でしょう
All the words handed over at the university
大学で渡されたすべての言葉
You're probably in the top 5% of rich people.
あなたはおそらく富裕層の上位 5% に入るでしょう。
out of 100 people
100個人當中
you're probably in fifth place
あなたはおそらく5位にいるでしょう
No. 6 is right
No.6が正解です
This is the rich man we imagined
これが私たちが想像していた金持ちです
there is a gap
ギャップがあります
But it appears on the tax information
ただし税務情報には記載されています
that's the number
それがその番号です
The member of the tax return information is you see you as long as each
納税申告書の会員の方は、それぞれの情報をご覧いただける限りご覧いただけます
It's not your money, it's a couple's money
それはあなたのお金ではありません、それは夫婦のお金です
As long as it exceeds 110,000, I don’t know if it’s not more than 100,000 in life
11万超えれば一生10万超えないかわからない
If it exceeds, you probably belong on the tax return.
それを超えている場合は、おそらく納税申告書に記載されている可能性があります。
10% of the rich
富裕層の10％は
10% of the 1% are rich
1%のうちの10%は金持ちだ
There is a gap between this and our common sense understanding.
これは私たちの常識的な理解との間にギャップがあります。
If your husband and wife together earn more than 110,000 a month
夫婦合わせて月収11万以上の場合
I think it's okay, it's okay
大丈夫だと思う、大丈夫
But it shouldn't be 10% of the money, right?
でもそれはお金の10％ではないはずですよね？
Also let's look at
も見てみましょう
In our data about that year
その年のデータでは
There are about 5.5 million total registered students
総登録世帯数は約550万世帯
The total number of family members has not reached 600,000
家族警備員の総数は60万人に達していない
About 595,000
約595,000
About 72.35% of all registered households
全登録世帯の約72.35％
In other words
言い換えると
There are approximately 3 out of 40,000 registered households in Taiwan
台湾の登録世帯数は 40,000 世帯のうち約 3 世帯です。
His monthly household income is less than 50,000 yuan
彼の世帯月収は5万元未満です
can you believe this number
この数字を信じられますか
Siwenwen is three families, among the 5.5 million households listed on the tax filing information,
シウェンウェンは、納税申告資料に記載されている550万世帯のうち、3世帯です。
Siwen is a family of three, and every couple earns less than 50,000 yuan.
シウェンさんは 3 人家族で、夫婦全員の収入は 5 万元未満です。
This is the tax return information, the presented information,
こちらは納税申告書、提示された情報です。
What does this mean? He will ask for a lot, and if he doesn’t have a lot of money, it’s like having a family with four Wen Wen,
これはどういう意味ですか? 彼はたくさんのものを要求します、そしてもし彼がたくさんのお金を持っていなければ、それはウェンウェン 4 人の家族を持つようなものです。
I can't earn 50,000 yuan every time, neither the account nor too big,
毎回5万元稼ぐことはできないし、口座も大きすぎるし、
Every time the husband and wife add up, or the wife does not have a job,
夫と妻が合計するたび、または妻が働かないたびに、
Anyway, it means that there are nearly 72.3, and I probably have four Wenwen families,
とにかく、それはほぼ 72.3 あることを意味し、おそらくウェンウェン家族は 4 人いるでしょう。
It’s probably less than 50,000 yuan every time. In other words, what you see here is that,
おそらく毎回5万元未満でしょう。
What I saw in the tax returns is that the rich people in Taiwan are not so rich,
納税申告書で私が見たのは、台湾の富裕層はそれほど裕福ではなく、
There are quite a lot of poor people in Taiwan, quite a lot,
台湾には貧しい人がたくさんいます、かなりたくさんいます、
This is in line with our common sense, our general understanding,
これは私たちの常識、一般的な理解と一致しています。
Injury is a big gap
怪我は大きなギャップだ
And what we just saw was a
そして、私たちが今見たのは、
tax filing information
納税情報
tax information
税金に関する情報
we want a
私たちが欲しいのは
He has a household ratings survey
彼は世帯評価調査を行っています
He also investigates with each other as a unit
彼はユニットとしてお互いに調査することもあります
each other as a unit
お互いをユニットとして
The two surveyed households
調査対象の2世帯
The definition sheet is different
定義シートが違う
It's the family rating of the doctrine department. He has a family unit.
それは教義部門の家族評価であり、彼には家族単位があります。
The first tax return has a household unit
最初の納税申告書には世帯単位があります
but if you think about it
でもよく考えてみれば
Which household has more units
どの世帯がより多くの戸数を持っているか
Because we know taxes are exhausting
税金が疲れるのは分かっているから
so he is exhausted
だから彼は疲れ果てている
so
それで
if you
もし、あんたが
If the child has money
子供にお金があれば
Of course you want him
もちろんあなたは彼が欲しいです
Do not declare together
一緒に宣言しないでください
right
右
Taxes will be lower if you file separately
別々に申告すると税金が安くなる
Because if you add up your child
なぜなら、子供を合計すると、
because taxes are exhausting
税金は疲れるから
So the added tax rate would be
したがって、追加税率は次のようになります。
The tax rate will be higher.
税率は高くなります。
so you can imagine
想像できるように
From a tax point of view
税金の観点から見ると
a family, a family
一個家庭,一個家庭
He may separate the child to hold
彼は子供を引き離して抱いてもらうかもしれない
Yes, separate and hug
そう、離れて抱きしめて
he won't drink him up and hug him
彼は彼を飲み干したり、抱きしめたりはしないだろう
So in theory
理論的には
Negative numbers on tax returns
納税申告書の負の数値
should be more than the family budget
家計よりも多くあるべきだ
the negative number defined by
によって定義される負の数
because you are in the family budget
家計の都合だから
when doing research
研究をするとき
In your family, for example
例えばあなたの家族の中で、
Your husband and wife have a child, and the child has a job
夫婦には子供がいて、子供は仕事をしている
he sees him as a
彼は彼を次のように見ています
but when filing taxes
しかし税金を申告するときは
That child may be separated from another life insurance
あの子は別の生命保険から切り離されるかもしれない
so in theory
だから理論的には
in theory
理論上
that is
あれは
Your
あなたの
Households subject to tax life insurance
生命保険の課税対象世帯
It should be better than the life insurance of family income and expenditure
家計の生命保険よりも良いはず
more housework
もっと家事をする
but anyway
とにかく
Among the data of the same year
同年のデータの中では
About 7.1 million households reported household income and expenditure
約710万世帯が家計の収入と支出を報告
what we just said
私たちが今言ったこと
Taxable life insurance approximately 500
所稅生保大概有500
or Wanhu
または万湖
If there are tax shares, there are about 1.6 million households
税負担があれば約160万世帯
legal exchange
法的交換
no tax return at all
税金の申告がまったくない
We know that we were promoting
私たちは宣伝していたことを知っています
Not when Ao was in health insurance
Oさんが健康保険に加入していたときはそうではなかった
There was an idea at the time that
当時はそういう考えがありました
We're going to use virtual income to calculate health insurance premiums
仮想所得を使って健康保険料を計算してみます
I think they were probably scared at the time, that is
おそらく当時は怖かったと思います。
many people get nothing
多くの人は何も得られない
or did not report or something
それとも報告しなかったのか何か
So I presume an income with you
だから私はあなたに収入があると推測します
virtual income
仮想収入
But Oboe's Picture
でもオーボエの絵は
The whole is to say from the data of 1994
全体は1994年のデータから言うと
then it feels like
そうすると次のように感じます
Hey, talk about rich people
ねえ、お金持ちのことを話してください
not so rich
それほど裕福ではない
you only need income
必要なのは収入だけ
As long as the monthly income is more than 110,000 points
月収11万ポイント以上であれば
Less than 120,000
120,000未満
You are probably one of 100 people
あなたはおそらく100人のうちの1人です
You'll be number 10
あなたは10位になります
you probably said
あなたはおそらく言ったでしょう
in other words
言い換えると
you're good
あなたは上手い
This is what we imagined
これが私たちが想像したものです
Couples add up every month
カップルは毎月合計します
Earn 110,000
110,000を稼ぐ
This is not much, is it?
これは大したことではありませんね。
As long as your family is a civil servant
家族が公務員である限り
Both husband and wife are civil servants
夫婦とも公務員です
probably earn that much
おそらくそれくらい稼げます
Because we see that there are almost three-quarters of more than 72 points
72点以上がほぼ4分の3あることが分かりますので
The family income is still less than 50,000 yuan per month
世帯収入はまだ月5万元未満
And what about this place, we said
それで、この場所はどうですか、と私たちは言いました
The household information reported should be larger than the negative household income information
報告される世帯情報はマイナスの世帯収入情報より大きくなければなりません
Suppose we make it equal
均等にするとします
You also see that there are probably very high negative numbers
また、負の数がほぼ同じであることもわかります。
No reporting at all, in other words, regardless of its legality
合法かどうかに関係なく、まったく報告しない
That is, it cannot be seen on the report data
つまり、レポートデータ上では確認できません。
This idea, this idea locks the tax machine
このアイデア、このアイデアは税務機械をロックします
It is to be full of seriousness, to erode the idea of ​​full seriousness
本気度に満ちること、本気度の概念を侵食すること
In the following example, it is necessary to obtain a confirmation indirectly
次の例では、間接的に確認を取得する必要があります。
an indirect confirmation
間接的な確認
This is general science
これは一般科学です
We know that before Ma Ying-jeou came to power in 2004
2004年に馬英九が権力を掌握する前に私たちはそれを知っています
While he was running for his credentials, he had an idea
彼は資格取得のために立候補しているときに、あるアイデアを思いつきました。
This idea, maybe the student gave him a catch
このアイデアはおそらく学生が彼に引っかかったのでしょう
How about this idea? The idea is that they have a N income credit with the United States.
このアイデアはどうでしょうか? そのアイデアは、米国との N 所得クレジットを持っているということです。
What is this? This means that you are serious about your work
これは何ですか? これは仕事に真剣に取り組んでいるという意味です
but your income is low
しかしあなたの収入は低いです
For example, I go to sell McDonald's and work many hours every month.
たとえば、私はマクドナルドの販売に行って、毎月何時間も働きます。
But the time to sell McDonald's is only 100 yuan
しかしマクドナルドを売る時はたったの100元だ
No matter how much I earn, no matter how many hours I work
どれだけ稼いでも、どれだけ働いても
The United States may also earn very low, and it is still very low now
米国の収入も非常に低い可能性があり、現在でも非常に低いです
What about this kind of person? The idea of ​​N income credit is this kind of person
こんな人はどうですか? Nインカムクレジットの考え方はこんな人です
I'll subsidize him
私は彼に補助金を出します
How to subsidize it? If you earn 100 yuan, I will subsidize you, for example, 20 yuan
どうやって補助しますか? 100元稼いだら、例えば20元補助します。
In other words, your income becomes 120 yuan
つまり、あなたの収入は120元になります。
This is the so-called N income credit
いわゆるNインカムクレジットです
This plan has been around for a long time in the United States.
この計画はアメリカでは長い間存在していた
But the Kundin era greatly expanded it
しかし、クンディン時代はそれを大幅に拡大しました
what is the main idea of ​​this thing
このことの主なアイデアは何ですか
The idea is that it doesn't just give you money
アイデアは、単にお金を与えるだけではないということです
On the contrary, it often has some regulations, that is,
それどころか、いくつかの規制があることがよくあります。
You have to work faster than a certain speed
一定の速度以上で作業する必要がある
For example, every other week to exceed an hour
たとえば、1 時間を超えるには隔週で
You can enjoy this benefit
この特典を享受できます
So it is not quite the same as the concept of social welfare
つまり社会福祉の概念とは全く同じではありません
Social welfare concept is you don't have money
社会福祉の概念はお金がないということです
shall i just give you the money
お金だけあげましょうか
It is not
そうではない
It's like saying you're serious about your work
仕事に真剣に取り組んでいると言っているようなものです
but don't know why
でもなぜだかわからない
you don't make much money
あなたはあまりお金を稼いでいません
so i subsidize you
だから私はあなたに補助金を出します
This program is now in the US in Europe
このプログラムは現在、米国およびヨーロッパで実施されています
are very popular
とても人気があります
Because this scheme is equivalent to
このスキームは以下と同等であるため、
Just make you willing to work
働く意欲を高めるだけです
This plan is equivalent to if you do not work
このプランは働いていない場合と同等です
Instead of getting the money
お金を得る代わりに
you have to work
あなたは働かなければなりません
And the working speed must exceed a certain standard
そして、作業速度は一定の基準を超えなければなりません
You can get this money
このお金を手に入れることができます
This idea was developed when Miku was running for office in 2004
このアイデアは、マンジュ氏が 2004 年に立候補していたときに思いつきました。
it brings up this thing
それはこのことを引き起こします
It really did when it came on stage
ステージに上がったときは本当にそうだった
these two
この二つ
what did you think
どう思いました
It's called the Working Income Supplement for all.
それは「すべての人のための勤労所得補足」と呼ばれるものです。
This is generally called the Jianping scheme
これは一般に建平スキームと呼ばれます
His target is over 20 years old
ターゲットは20歳以上
did not reach the age of 65
65歳に達していなかった
full primary earner
完全な主な稼ぎ手
For example, Mr. and Mrs.
たとえば、Mr. and Mrs.
His personal annual salary is below 300,000
個人年収は30万以下
full time worker
フルタイム労働者
So you see he has a rule that says
つまり、彼には次のようなルールがあることがわかります。
your annual salary is lower
あなたの年収はもっと低いです
but full time
でもフルタイム
In other words, you didn't mean guess what?
言い換えれば、推測するという意味ではありません。
It means that you are really doing work.
本気で仕事をしているということですね。
The working hours are still high
労働時間はまだまだ長い
But the money you earn is very low
でも稼げるお金はとても少ないです
i will help you
私はあなたを助ける
How did you do it?
どうやってやったのですか？
At that time the practice was
当時の練習は、
Because he is a social welfare bearer
社会福祉の担い手だから
So the Ministry of the Interior is in charge
つまり内務省が担当する
How does the Ministry of the Interior use it?
内務省はそれをどのように使用しますか?
He took the taxation center of the Ministry of Finance as the
彼は大蔵省の税務センターを担当した。
Based on fiscal and tax data from 1990
1990 年の財政および税データに基づく
compare
比較
able to screen out qualified candidates
資格のある候補者を選別することができる
And then through the county and city governments
そして郡や市政府を通じて
Active Program Application
アクティブなプログラム アプリケーション
to those who qualify
資格のある方へ
in other words
言い換えると
It uses this tax information
この税務情報を使用します
you go to filter
あなたはフィルターに行きます
Assuming you are a full child worker
あなたが完全な児童労働者であると仮定すると、
then your personal salary
じゃあ個人の給料は
this means
これの意味は
your main paycheck
あなたの主な給料
Personal annual salary is low
個人の年収は低い
For example, less than 300,000
たとえば、300,000 未満
I'm like
私はまるで
Active Planning Fact Sheet for you
あなたのためのアクティブプランニングファクトシート
I'm getting ready now
今準備中です
take this NNK
このNNKを受け取ってください
of the money you make
あなたが稼いだお金のうち
My government will subsidize you some money
私の政府はあなたにいくらかのお金を補助します
the idea
このアイデア
we found a big problem
私たちは大きな問題を見つけました
this problem
この問題
we would like
私たちそうしたい
this policy
このポリシー
not that you apply
あなたが応募するわけではありません
No
いいえ
It is to filter from fiscal and taxation data
財政および税務データからフィルタリングすることです
then look at you
それからあなたを見てください
not enough hands
手が足りない
I will take the initiative to inform you that
率先してお知らせさせていただきます
You are eligible to receive this money
あなたにはこのお金を受け取る資格があります
so not
そうじゃない
in other words
言い換えると
You don't even need to apply.
申請する必要もありません。
It informs about proactive programs
プロアクティブなプログラムについてお知らせします
just for you
貴方のために
So the government took the initiative
そこで政府が主導権を握った
Probably the biggest feature of this contraband plan
おそらくこの密輸計画の最大の特徴は
not you to apply
申請するのはあなたではありません
then go up to filter
次にフィルターに進みます
But the place is out of the game
しかし、その場所はゲームの対象外です
Probably not as good as the so-called Chinese
おそらくいわゆる中国人ほどではないでしょう
Therefore, the application materials have an authenticity
したがって、申請書類には真実性があります。
There is a problem with this information
この情報には問題があります
For example, the China Times on October 3, 1997
たとえば、1997 年 10 月 3 日のチャイナ タイムズ
it has a report
報告書があります
This program appears as the subsidy object for the factory director
この制度は工場長に対する補助金の対象となります。
Quite a lot
かなりたくさん
because you look
あなたが見てるから
If you go to subsidize
補助金を出すなら
Maybe through the Lichang or something to get to know him
李昌か何かを通じて彼と知り合うかもしれない
you have the qualifications
あなたには資格があります
The consular district on the left is small
左側の領事館地区は小さい
The consular district on the left is of course small
左側の領事館地区はもちろん小さいです
is this guy rich
この人は金持ちですか
Is it rich to get this?
これを手に入れるのはお金持ちですか？
probably small
おそらく小さい
So you go and see
だから行って見なさい
local newspaper at the time
当時の地元新聞
In many places, the prophecy is directly elected
多くの場所で、予言は直接選出される
why
なぜ
why he can get
なぜ彼は手に入れることができるのか
i can't take it
我慢できない
this problem happens
この問題が起こる
I have no money than him
私は彼よりお金がありません
why he can get
なぜ彼は手に入れることができるのか
i can't take it
我慢できない
so at that time
だからその時は
local and central
地方と中央
For example, the Southern Legislative Council at that time
たとえば、当時の南部立法評議会。
just throw the Ministry of the Interior
内務省を放り投げてください
Disbursed on the practice of subsidizing Hunan
湖南省の実践に対する補助金に関するアカウントを発行しました
How about that's the Ministry of the Interior?
内務省はどうですか？
that's computer choice
それはコンピューターの選択です
I'm a changing profile
私はプロフィールを変更中です
I'm choosing
私が選んでいます
So what about this plan?
それで、この計画はどうでしょうか？
It's like being exposed
まるで暴露されてるみたいだ
This code tax is actually full of problems
このコード税は実は問題だらけだ
It reflects only one of the Chinese code tax data
中国のコード税データの 1 つだけを反映しています。
I especially wanted to study the Jianmin plan at that time.
当時私は特に建民計画を研究したいと思っていました。
I also went to the Ministry of the Interior to ask him for advice.
私も内務省に相談に行きました。
Do you have any information
何か情報はありますか
Then how can I refer to
ではどうやって参照すればよいのでしょうか
What about the Ministry of the Interior?
内務省はどうですか？
He deleted all the information about the Jianmin plan
彼はジャンミン計画に関する情報をすべて削除した
as if this never happened
まるでそんなことは起こらなかったかのように
Because this seems to be a very embarrassing thing
とても恥ずかしいことだと思われるので、
yes embarrassing thing
そう、恥ずかしいこと
It's not a benefit
それは利益ではありません
My plan is
私の計画は
So all the information about the Jianmin project
Jianmin プロジェクトに関するすべての情報
you are online now
あなたは今オンラインです
as if this never happened
まるでそんなことは起こらなかったかのように
never happened
絶対に起こらない
But what I'm saying is
しかし、私が言っていることは、
Let's see from the data
データから見てみましょう
90 years of information to see
90年分の情報が見られる
we have strong doubts
私たちは強い疑念を抱いています
This Solo tax deep insurance is quite substantial
この Solo の税金保証は非常に充実しています。
You only need to earn more than 110,000 points every month
毎月110,000ポイント以上貯めるだけでOK
Less than 120,000
120,000未満
You're probably in the 10% rich
あなたはおそらく10％の富裕層に属します
The rich man we imagine is for you to check
私たちが想像するお金持ちはあなたに確認してもらいたい
In other words, your husband and wife are probably not too bad.
つまり、あなたのご夫婦はそれほど悪くないのかもしれません。
For example, workers
たとえば、労働者
you don't want to be superior
何か優れたことをしたくないのですか
It's probably up to that standard.
おそらくその水準に達していると思われます。
Then additionally we see
次に、さらに次のようになります。
Less than 50,000 yuan
5万元未満
A bunch of people didn't reach 50,000 yuan
5万元に届かない人も多かった
Nearly three quarters more than 72 points
ほぼ4分の3が72ポイントを超えている
The monthly salary is less than 50,000 yuan
月給は5万円未満
In addition, we report
また、ご報告させていただきます
Comparing the data of the doctrine number with the tax declaration data
教義番号のデータと納税申告データの比較
we have reason to believe
私たちには信じる理由がある
There are probably more than 1.6 million households
おそらく160万世帯以上あるでしょう
Probably the tax system has not grasped it at all
おそらく税制はそれを全く把握していない
It's legal and illegal, it's fine if you don't declare it
合法も違法も申告しなくても大丈夫
the concept in this
この中のコンセプトは
not on the plan
計画にない
I feel like getting a confirmation
確証が得られる気がする
Because the characteristic of this program is that
なぜなら、このプログラムの特徴は、
you don't have to apply
申請する必要はありません
I use the data
データを使用します
Maybe the Ministry of the Interior didn't even think of saying
おそらく内務省はそんなことを考えもしなかったのでしょう。
have this problem
この問題があります
Because how he repays is to let you go to Hong Kong
だって彼の返済方法はあなたを香港に行かせることだから
This compensation is for his authenticity
この補償は彼の誠実さに対するものです
he won't have this problem
彼にはこの問題はないでしょう
Because if you have no money, you really have no money.
お金がなければ、本当にお金がないからです。
But Hua Xuedao said the subsidy object
しかし、華雪道は補助金は反対だと述べた
may not be right
正しくないかもしれない
Because the left and right fields are small
左右のフィールドが小さいので
this guy is rich
この人は金持ちだ
he drives the car
彼は車を運転します
You can probably tell that he lives in a house.
おそらく彼が家に住んでいることがわかります。
why he can get
なぜ彼は手に入れることができるのか
i can't take it
我慢できない
So if you check the newspapers at that time
それで、当時の新聞をチェックしてみると、
Many local councils have a consultation
多くの地方議会が協議を行っている
because it's going to spread
蔓延するから
This guy can take
この人なら取れるよ
I guess he's probably going to be gone.
おそらく彼はいなくなると思います。
to distribute
配布する
Maybe the left and right fields are small
左右のフィールドが小さいのかもしれません
say this can take
これはかかると言う
why can't i get it
なぜ手に入らないのか
Even if it's a big problem
たとえそれが大きな問題だったとしても
But the whole old man
しかし、老人全体が
i hope i mean
それが意味することを願っています
There is a Matchity
マッチングがあります
This Matchity means
この一致が意味するのは、
Shou Luo Tax Division
寿羅税務課
More imaginary Shouluo tax
さらに架空の寿洛税
That's right
それはそうです
Obviously there are a lot of designs in Taiwan's income
台湾の収入には明らかにデザインがたくさんあります
did not grasp at all
全く把握できなかった
Like I said we can get hold of now
私が言ったように、今すぐ手に入れることができます
Most everything has buckle corners and flat sheets
ほとんどすべてのものにバックルコーナーとフラットシートが付いています
Flat single with buckle angle
バックルアングル付きフラットシングル
In other words, if you're filing your taxes, you're underage.
言い換えれば、税金を申告している場合、あなたは未成年です。
If you are required to file taxes
税金の申告が必要な場合
All your information is meat
あなたの情報はすべて肉です
All those things are produced and all of them are mastered
それらすべてが生み出され、すべてがマスターされる
what is that
それは何ですか
It's like your salary
それはあなたの給料のようなものです
For example, the company sends you encouragement
たとえば、会社から激励が届く。
or what bank pays your interest
またはどの銀行が利子を払ってくれるのか
Those are all SER parties
それはSERパーティーです
The bank will pay you a salary
銀行が給料を払ってくれる
when the interest
利子のとき
He will take the initiative to notify
彼は率先して知らせるだろう
the irs says
国税は言う
How much interest do I give him?
私は彼にどれくらいの興味を与えますか？
or when the company wants to pay dividends
または会社が配当を支払いたい場合
He will take the initiative to notify
彼は率先して知らせるだろう
the irs says
国税は言う
how much encouragement does this guy get
この男はどれだけ励まされるだろうか
This is all with SER Party
これはすべて SER パーティーによるものです
Once there is a SER Party
SER パーティーが開催されると
you probably won't be able to escape
あなたはおそらく逃げられないでしょう
Because it is equal to the national tax unit
国税単位と等しいので
fully grasped
完全に把握された
But now the problem is no Street Party
しかし今の問題はストリートパーティーがないことです
Taiwan can't do it well
台湾はうまくいかない
Because of Taiwan when we were young
幼い頃台湾のせいで
Taiwan has a characteristic
台湾には特別なものがあります
Middle-aged and old enterprises are particularly developed
中高年企業が特に発展している
So I think the question
それで私は質問だと思います
It's not about the water
水の話じゃないよ
because i think it's
そうだと思うから
structural problems
構造的な問題
it has two structural problems
2つの構造上の問題がある
like i said
私が言ったように
One problem, of course, is that our middle-aged and old enterprises
もちろん、問題の 1 つは、中高年の企業が
It's us Tang Da
私たちタンダーです
These are all year round
これらは一年中あります
Live all year round
一年中住んでいます
i used to say
私はよく言っていた
I am a student
私は学生です
He is the person expected at the beginning of the year
彼は今年の初めに期待されている人物です
he once told me
彼はかつて私にこう言いました
It's really useless to catch them.
捕まえても本当に無駄です。
useless
使い物にならない
He might just declare bankruptcy or something
彼は破産か何かを宣言するかもしれない
And here is a profile
そしてプロフィールはこちら
This data also tells us that
このデータは次のことも示しています
this is really not easy
これは本当に簡単ではありません
Because the statistics of the United States
アメリカの統計だから
He says it's not easy to be a solo business
彼は個人事業は簡単ではないと言う
This is the so-called sale improvement
いわゆる売上向上です
It's like being your own boss.
まるで自分の上司になったようなものです。
look
見て
His data is about 57%
彼のデータは約 57%
will be exposed
暴露されるだろう
In other words, for moviegoing friends
つまり、映画を見に行く友人にとっては、
not one from taiwan
台湾からは一人もいない
it's hard for you to grasp
あなたには理解するのが難しいです
The United States has based on their data
米国はデータに基づいて、
estimated
推定
It's like researching it
それを研究しているようなものです
About half of the income
収入の半分くらい
Like one hundred yuan, about fifty-seven
100元くらい、57元くらい
you probably didn't get it
おそらく理解できなかったでしょう
so this is a
これは
tantamount to a real problem
現実の問題に等しい
real problem
本当の問題
You can't shoot that every day
毎日は撮れないよ
So everyone gives him every day
だからみんなが毎日彼にあげます
praise him
彼を褒める
And the atmosphere is really a lot
そして雰囲気は本当にたくさんです
In fact, if you go out of Taiwan now
実際、今台湾から出国すると、
everyone is doing business
誰もがビジネスをしています
angry so much
とても怒っている
You can't make every family smaller
すべての家族を小さくすることはできない
some more famous
もう少し有名な
For example, when I was young, didn’t I have Fuhang Soymilk?
たとえば、私が子供の頃、扶杭豆乳を持っていませんでしたか？
Fuhang soy milk is famous
府杭豆乳が有名
When I was young, this family was full of famous
私が幼い頃、この家族は有名人でいっぱいでした
villain is good
悪役は良いよ
Of course he will give you the account
もちろんアカウントも教えてくれますよ
he can see
彼は見える
look , you sold so much
ほら、そんなに売れたんだよ
You paid taxes so why so little
あなたは税金を払っているのに、なぜそんなに少ないのか
he has reason
彼には理由がある
but that is to say
しかし、それはつまり
So he's like those too famous
だから彼はあまりにも有名な人たちと同じだ
probably not so good
もしかしたらあまり良くないかもしれない
Because the national tax is of course small
国税は当然少ないので
Your business is very good
あなたのビジネスはとても順調です
outside of those
それらの外で
Check each one for you
それぞれをチェックしてください
So this is a problem, Taiwan comes out
だから台湾が出てくるかどうかが問題だ
So if in the process of enterprise development
したがって、企業の発展の過程にある場合
For example, getting bigger and bigger, for example, look at
たとえば、どんどん大きくなっていきます。たとえば、見てください。
There used to be a lot of grocery stores in Taiwan
台湾には昔は食料品店がたくさんありました
That tax may be difficult to control
その税金をコントロールするのは難しいかもしれない
But when you become 711, it's different
でも711になると違う
In the case of 711, the national tax unit will fully grasp
711の場合は国税局が完全に把握するだろう
Because in the case of 711, it unifies itself and needs to control it internally
711の場合は統一して内部で管理する必要があるため
In terms of internal control, it must have a document so that false reports cannot be made
内部統制の観点から虚偽の報告ができないよう文書化する必要がある
Therefore, throughout the development process, if
したがって、開発プロセス全体を通じて、
Change to 711 for grocery stores
食料品店の場合は 711 に変更します
We know that this kind of tax will increase
この種の税金が増えることはわかっています
Because the grocery store is difficult to control, 711 probably controls the tax
食料品店の管理は難しいため、711 が税金を管理している可能性があります
Taiwan has such a problem
台湾にはこんな問題がある
In addition, I think there is a problem that
さらに、次のような問題もあると思います。
Taiwan is an open and small economy
台湾は開放的で小規模な経済国です
locks out easily
簡単にロックアウトされる
All I talk about is that I don't know
私が話しているのは、私が知らないということだけです
Can this be used as an indicator?
これは指標として使えますか？
For example, the United News Network has a reward
たとえば、United News Network には次のような特典があります。
Commonwealth Magazine joined an international consortium of investigative journalists in July 2003
コモンウェルス・マガジンは、2003 年 7 月に調査ジャーナリストの国際連合に参加しました。
Aiming at the status of overseas offshore assets in the Dazhong area
大中地区における海外オフショア資産の地位を目指す
A six-month investigation
6か月にわたる調査
According to this decrypted data
この復号化されたデータによると
Overseas offshore asset holders in the Dazhong area probably
おそらく大中地区の海外オフショア資産保有者
Accounted for 35% of all data
全データの 35% を占める
Among them Taiwan
その中には台湾も
about this many
これくらいの数
1.5 times that of Hong Kong
香港の1.5倍
China's 1.5
中国の1.5
The Union of Journalists
該記者聯盟
Taiwanese use tax shelter computers far more than Hong Kong
台湾は香港よりはるかに多くの税務署のコンピューターを利用しています
Repay here
ここで返済してください
but maybe
だけど、たぶん
There are different
違いがある
an interpretation
解釈
not as good as you can imagine
想像できるほど良くない
Because many people in Taiwan do business outside
台湾では外でビジネスをする人が多いので
I understand that many of them just set up an account overseas.
海外にアカウントを開設したばかりの人も多いようです。
this account
このアカウント
so
それで
Taiwan to tax the rich
台湾が富裕層に課税へ
not as easy as we imagined
私たちが想像していたほど簡単ではありません
From the point of view of education
教育という観点から見ると
talk about what you get
あなたが得たものについて話す
very quickly
非常に迅速に
From an efficiency point of view
効率の観点から
It should have been lower tax rate
もっと税率下げるべきだった
because you can imagine
想像できるから
A piece of land is over there
あそこに土地があるよ
how do you give it the gram
グラムはどうやって与えるのですか
it's the land
それは土地です
The tax should be higher
税金はもっと高くてもいいよ
on the other hand
一方で
it equals in and out quickly
それはすぐにインとアウトに等しくなります
you give it a little boost
あなたはそれを少し後押しします
it just ran away
それはただ逃げただけです
tax loss
欠損金
Very serious
非常に深刻
such tax
そのような税金
Tax rates should have been lower
税率はもっと低いはずだった
From the point of view of education
教育という観点から見ると
Taiwan is an open economy again
台湾は再び開放経済へ
Then Taiwan has another problem
台湾にはまた別の問題がある
That is to say, it does not have diplomatic relations with many countries.
つまり、多くの国と国交を結んでいないのです。
no diplomatic relations at all
外交関係は全くありません
Sometimes we can pass an equal to
場合によっては等しいものを渡すことができます
an exchange of information
情報交換
For example, in the tax department
たとえば、税務署では
can be mastered
マスターできる
For example, between you and the mainland
たとえばあなたと本土の間
pay an information exchange
お金を払って情報交換をする
I know the money you make in mainland China
あなたが中国本土で稼いでいるお金は知っています
You, a Taiwanese businessman, made money in mainland China
台湾の実業家であるあなたは中国本土で儲けました
I know how much money I make
自分がどれだけ稼いでいるのか知っています
But Taiwan has a problem
しかし台湾にも問題はある
That is to say, it has no political relations with many countries.
つまり、多くの国と政治的関係はありません。
so at this point
だからこの時点では
It's not so easy now
今はそれほど簡単ではありません
have faced a difficulty
困難に直面しました
So it is not so easy for rich people in Taiwan
つまり、台湾の富裕層にとってはそれほど簡単ではないのです
then we have a discussion this afternoon
それから今日の午後は話し合います
It's Zhu Qingying's luck
それは朱清英の幸運だ
He's been in therapy for financial problems lately
彼は最近経済的問題で治療を受けている
he's going to do a study
彼は勉強するつもりです
what is this research
この研究は何ですか
That is to say, the top one percent
つまり上位1パーセントは
For example, out of 100 people
たとえば、100人のうち、
You are one of the highest version of people
あなたは人間の最も高いバージョンの一人です
he earns
彼は稼いでいる
that is
あれは
How much of the 100 yuan is the top one percent of the income
上位 1 パーセントの収入は 100 元のうちいくらですか
For example, earning materials is about 13 yuan
例えば、素材稼ぎは約13元
In other words, among the 100 yuan
つまり、100元のうち、
It is equal to the 100 yuan of our whole society
これは私たちの社会全体の100元に相当します
The top one percent is about 13 yuan
上位1パーセントは約13元
For example, on the data
たとえば、データ上では
I don't know the details, he remembers
詳細は分からないが、彼は覚えている
But there is an interesting phenomenon
しかし、面白い現象があります
let's draw
描きましょう
2012 words
2012年の言葉
because in 2008 words
なぜなら2008年の言葉で
We know the financial tsunami
私たちは金融津波を知っています
During the financial tsunami, the top one percent
金融津波の最中、上位1パーセントは
you can draw
あなたは描くことができます
So we know that when the financial tsunami
つまり、金融津波が起きたとき、
there is a decision
決定があります
He originally said that among the 100 yuan
彼は当初、100元のうちに
up to 13 percent
最大13パーセント
In that year, you may only earn 7 yuan or 8 yuan
その年に稼げるのは7元か8元だけ
so
それで
In addition, we just made an interesting declaration
さらに、興味深い宣言をしました。
In 2012, we are ashamed
2012年、私たちは恥ずかしながら
This proportion is also falling
この割合も下がってきています
then let's find out
それでは調べてみましょう
What happened in 2012
2012年に何が起こったのか
We know that happened to be the secretary of the treasury at the time
私たちは、彼がたまたま当時財務長官だったことを知っています
Who is that called?
それは誰と呼ばれていますか？
I've been going there also with the female treasury secretary
私も女性財務長官と一緒にそこへ行ってきました
Isn't he going to engrave the forehand tax?
彼は前払い税を刻むつもりではないでしょうか？
carve a forehand tax
前払い税を彫る
You see, that year also made his proportion drop.
ご存知のように、その年は彼の割合も低下しました。
equal to
に等しい
That is to say, to boil the eyes in the mouth, I think it means to say
つまり、口の中で目を沸騰させる、ということだと思います。
Taiwanese want to tax the rich
台湾人は富裕層への課税を望んでいる
not so easy
そう簡単ではない
they have a way
彼らには方法がある
there are ways
方法はあります
It's like if you want to tax him
彼に税金を課したいようなものだ
he ran to show you
彼はあなたに見せようと走って行きました
So instead of a feature dispute
したがって、機能に関する論争の代わりに
This is the responsibility of making money
これはお金を稼ぐ責任です
He should pay more tax
彼はもっと税金を払うべきだ
From a business point of view
ビジネスの観点から
It's not that easy to see
そんなに簡単に見られるものではないよ
So I think it's two structural
つまり、2つの構造があると思います
kind of question
一種の質問
The first is greed for small and medium-sized enterprises
一つ目は中小企業の貪欲さ
Tedo
手戸
Everyone is their own boss
誰もが自分の上司です
did you notice
気づきましたか
your relatives and friends
あなたの親戚や友人
As long as it is a small and medium-sized enterprise
中小企業である限り
Generally speaking
一般的に言えば
don't do too badly
あまり悪いことをしないでください
His life is probably more humorous than yours
彼の人生はおそらくあなたの人生よりもユーモラスです
but when it comes to paying taxes
しかし税金を払うとなると
You guarantee that he pays less tax than you
あなたは彼があなたよりも少ない税金を支払うことを保証します
compare your life to words
自分の人生を言葉に例えてみる
for example
例えば
his house is better than yours
彼の家はあなたの家よりも良いです
eat better than you
あなたよりもよく食べる
anything is better than you
あなたよりも優れているものは何もありません
But you have to actually ask him how much he pays in taxes
でも実際に彼に税金をいくら払っているのか聞いてみる必要がある
look
見て
You pay the new leader
あなたは新しいリーダーにお金を払います
have you ever thought about
今まで考えたことがありますか
I guess they are higher
そちらの方が高いと思います
not high
高くない
and much taller
そしてずっと背が高い
So I think it's one of those in Taiwan
だから、それは台湾のものの一つだと思います
tantamount to a structural problem
構造的な問題に等しい
the one we just talked about
私たちが今話したもの
american words
アメリカの言葉
in fact internationally
実際に国際的には
There are 100 of them
100個あります
57 run away
57 逃げる
So express this thing
だからこのことを表現してください
Actually it is not easy to grow
実は育てるのは簡単ではない
has its difficulty
難しさがある
For example, unless you invest a lot of resources
たとえば、多額のリソースを投資しない限り、
If you invest a lot of resources
多額のリソースを投資した場合
Say you receive a dollar
1ドルを受け取ったとします
You have to pay fifty cents to collect
集めるには50セント支払わなければなりません
It's not worth it
それはそれだけの価値はありません
So there is a structural problem
つまり構造的に問題がある
in other words
言い換えると
There are many such series
こういうシリーズはたくさんあるよ
In addition, Taiwan is open to Qingjing
さらに、台湾は清京にオープンです
Code is easy to flow out
コードが流出しやすい
You have to tax some people
一部の人々に税金を課さなければならない
won't make it easy for you
あなたにとってそれは簡単ではありません
so overall
全体的にそう
I think code tax
コード税だと思います
It might not be as good as we imagined.
私たちが想像していたほど良くないかもしれません。
This is my main message
これが私のメインメッセージです
Code tax strictly speaking
厳密に言えばコード税
It is a
それは
In theory a nice tax system
理論的には素晴らしい税制
because it can be tailored to your individual situation
個々の状況に合わせて調整できるので、
Make a design for you to measure the customer tax
顧客税を測定するためのデザインを作成します
But in practice
しかし実際には
I think at least in Taiwan
少なくとも台湾ではそう思う
Let's look at the data
データを見てみましょう
have a big problem
大きな問題がある
It's quite different from what we imagined.
私たちが想像していたものとはかなり違います。
i think this
私はこう思います
Not that it's a problem I don't work on
それは私が取り組んでいない問題というわけではありません
it's a structural problem
それは構造的な問題です
structural
結構性
If this is the case, we may have to think differently about the design of broken characters, and get out of the situation
この場合、壊れた文字のデザインについて別の方法を考えて、この状況から抜け出す必要があるかもしれません。
It cannot be said that we will only strengthen the reform of broken gloves.
壊れた手袋の改革だけを強化するとは言えません。
may have a different idea
違う考えがあるかもしれない
So the underlying idea is that we know how to break into pieces
つまり、根底にある考え方は、私たちは粉々に砕く方法を知っているということです
Probably a space that can be considered
おそらく検討できるスペースです
Let's take a look at this, of course everyone knows it
これを見てみましょう、もちろん誰もがそれを知っています
That newspaper is very big
あの新聞はとても大きいです
That is to say, global housing prices are affordable
つまり、世界の住宅価格は手頃な価格である
Since Taipei City is higher than Hong Kong
台北市は香港より高いので
It is the house price glove ratio
住宅価格グローブ比率です
That is to say, the price of the gloves you earn is compared with your gloves
つまり、あなたが稼いだ手袋の価格とあなたの手袋が比較されます。
also more than several times
それも数回以上
more than several times
数回以上
You see us ordinary people in London, Los Angeles
ロンドンやロサンゼルスにいる私たち普通の人が見えますね
These are famous cities anyway
とにかく有名な都市です
we are now taller than that
私たちは今それよりも背が高くなりました
It's really hard to imagine a thing
何かを想像するのは本当に難しい
In addition, if we know it, we will announce it now
また分かりましたら今すぐ発表させていただきます
Why announce land restrictions? Mainly the so-called land tax increase
なぜ土地制限を発表するのか?主にいわゆる土地税の増税です。
This has a notice of land restrictions
これには土地制限の通知があります
It is the tax authority for landowners
地主に対する税務当局です
It is used as the basis for land value appreciation when the land is sold and sold
土地を売買する際の地価上昇の根拠として利用されます。
it is tuned once a year
年に一度調整されます
now you can come and look for it
今、あなたは来てそれを探すことができます
fine
大丈夫
That is to say, the tone is not as low as imagined.
つまり、想像していたほど低音ではないということです。
The announcement limit is equal to the announcement limit adjustment, which is close to the market price, about 80 or so
発表限度額は発表限度額の調整額と等しく、市場価格に近い約 80 ドル程度です。
Like Taipei City to 89
台北市のような89
New Taipei City to 89
新北市が89に
Anyway, other places are okay
他の場所はどうでもいいけど
This is when we know that you buy and sell land
あなたが土地を売買していることを知ったのはこの時です
There is a benchmark for the course
コースにはベンチマークがあります
Curriculum Benchmarks
カリキュラムのベンチマーク
but let's look at another
しかし、別のものを見てみましょう
what would you look like if you held land
もしあなたが土地を所有していたらどうなるでしょうか
This gap is quite big
このギャップはかなり大きいです
What is the main purpose of announcing the land price?
地価を発表する主な目的は何ですか？
Announcement of land ownership by all persons during the land holding period
土地保有期間中の全員の土地所有権の公表
It has to pay a tax, which is the announced land price
公示地価である税金を支払わなければなりません
We just bought and sold land, you have to pay a land increase tax, land value-added tax
土地を売買しただけなので、土地増収税、土地付加価値税を支払わなければなりません
But if you own land, for example, if you own a house, you probably own land
しかし、あなたが土地を所有している場合、たとえば家を所有している場合は、おそらく土地を所有していることになります。
For land, you have to pay a land value tax
土地の場合は地価税を支払わなければなりません
The land value tax is adjusted every three years
地価税は3年ごとに調整されます
In other words, only once every three years
つまり、調整は 3 年に 1 回だけです
And you see, the gap between the market price and the market price is quite large, the gap between the market price is quite large
そして、ご存知のとおり、市場価格と市場価格の間のギャップは非常に大きく、市場価格とのギャップは非常に大きいです
In other words, if you own the house, especially the land
つまり、家、特に土地を所有している場合
The holding cost is not high, simply put
簡単に言えば、保有コストは高くありません
If we discuss it with our colleagues, maybe you own a car
同僚と話し合えば、もしかしたらあなたは車を所有しているかもしれません
You pay more taxes than you pay on owning a house
家を所有するよりも多くの税金を払っている
In other words, what you pay every year is what you pay for your car
言い換えれば、あなたが毎年支払う金額が車の代金と同じになります。
Not a license plate tax, but also fuel fees
ナンバープレート税ではなく、燃料費もかかります
Then the sum might be higher than the one you paid, even the tax you paid with a house
その場合、その金額はあなたが支払った金額、さらには家を買うために支払った税金よりも高くなる可能性があります
is this really reasonable
これは本当に合理的ですか
it's not very reasonable
それはあまり合理的ではありません
Let's take a look at this picture and tell us that
この写真を見て、それを伝えましょう。
If we take three years and 100 years in 2000 as a machine
2000年に3年と100年を機械としてみると
Check out this change
この変更を確認してください
This is an index of a new house
新築住宅のインデックスです
That is three years and 120 years in 2000
2000年では3年と120年になります。
You can see the index words
索引語が見れます
If the red is the index
赤がインデックスの場合
Of course it has risen to about 270 now
もちろん今は270くらいまで上がってます
about 270
約270
But also with this 2000 three-year 100 units
ただし、この 2000 の 3 年 100 ユニットでも、
you use a land appreciation tax
あなたは土地評価税を使用します
Or underground tax house tax
あるいはアンダーグラウンド・タックス・ハウス・タックス
You see, it might be better to increase the tax on this land
ほら、この土地の税金を上げたほうがいいかもしれない
Land tax increase should be this, but unpredictable
土地税増税はこうなるはずだが予測不能
About 160 170
約160 170
But this underground tax
しかし、この地下税は
just to put it simply
簡単に言えば
When we were young, the modernization rule increased the price and returned the goods
私たちが若い頃、近代化政策により価格が上がり、商品は返品されました
It is obvious from this soil
この土壌を見れば一目瞭然
The price increase did not return the goods at all
値上げしても商品が全く戻ってこない
Because it's so long
とても長いので
but the really broken parts
でも本当に壊れた部分は
It's quite a big difference from before.
以前とはかなり大きな違いです。
quite a big gap
かなり大きなギャップ
I just said it was
そうだと言ったばかりです
Our government is violating the constitution
私たちの政府は憲法に違反しています
tantamount to violating the constitution
憲法違反に等しい
to grow back
成長して戻る
Tell you from this picture
この写真からお伝えします
It didn't last long at all.
全然長くは続かなかった。
big gap
大きなギャップ
OK
OK
what we just said
私たちが今言ったこと
There is a problem with the lock
ロックに問題があります
Not as good as expected
期待したほど良くない
what to do
何をすべきか
My idea of ​​paying is to say
お金を払うという私の考えは、
Property tax should be a good tax object
固定資産税は適切な課税対象であるべきだ
tax object
税金の対象
think about it
考えてみてください
He escaped in the lock
彼は鍵の中に逃げた
i didn't pay
私は支払わなかった
but he might go buy some real estate
でも彼は不動産を買いに行くかもしれない
The real estate is right there
不動産はすぐそこにある
Real estate is something you can see and touch.
不動産は目で見て触れられるものです。
not the same as locked
ロックされているのと同じではありません
You have to think about how much this person has locked up
この人がどれだけのロックを持っているかを考える必要があります
it's hard for you to imagine
あなたには想像するのが難しいです
We call Property Pharma Center's Property Declaration Pharmacy
私たちは Property Pharma Center の Property Declaration Pharmacy と呼んでいます
The rules may not be so accurate
ルールはそれほど正確ではないかもしれません
But property I think is pretty accurate
しかし、プロパティはかなり正確だと思います
Because any property you make is where
なぜなら、あなたが作った財産はどこにあるのかということです。
it is very clear
それはとても明らかです
Moreover, our small Taiwan adopts a registration system
また、私たちの小さな台湾は登録制を採用しています
That is, you probably wouldn't easily register in someone else's name, would you?
ということは、簡単に他人の名前では登録しないでしょうね。
Presumably your property is registered in your name
おそらくあなたの不動産はあなたの名前で登録されているでしょう
That property is clearly over there
その物件は明らかにあそこにあります
over there
そちら側
So I think this should be taught to him
だからこれを彼に教えるべきだと思う
Equal to that you may be in the code so not paid
コード内にいる可能性があるため、支払われないのと同じです
Now the property is over there
今、その物件はあそこにあります
And we call it property, what characteristics does it have?
それを財産と呼びますが、どのような特徴があるのでしょうか?
it's right there
それはすぐそこにあります
over there
そちら側
what your class rules say
あなたのクラスのルールは何ですか
If it's a heavy lesson
重いレッスンの場合
It's also a lesson
それも教訓です
or become more difficult to move
あるいは動きにくくなる
But now the property is over there
でも今はその物件はあそこにある
What is the characteristic of this in terms of taxation?
これは税制上どのような特徴があるのでしょうか。
This is distortion is relatively small this tax
これは歪みが比較的小さい今回の税金です
because it's right there
それはすぐそこにあるから
it may of course have a sequela
もちろん後遺症が残る可能性もある
It's what you might think of after your class
レッスン後に思うこと
That means you step on the past to accumulate property again
つまり、過去を踏みにじって再び財産を蓄積するということです。
not so good
あまりよくない
have this sequelae
この後遺症がある
But now it's over there
でも今はそこにある
over there
そちら側
It's worth the lesson
レッスンを受ける価値はあります
well worth the lesson
レッスンする価値は十分にあります
So this is equivalent to saying
したがって、これは次のように言うのと同じです
That is to say, the pieces of your hand didn’t reach that part
つまりそこには手の破片が届かなかった
your property is visible
あなたの財産が見えるようになる
Is it possible to use the broken part of the property
壊れた物件の一部を使用することは可能ですか
To make up for the lack of broken hands
壊れた手の不足を補うために
And it means that our small financial distribution is uneven now
そしてそれは、私たちの小規模な財政分配が現在不均一であることを意味します
Uneven financial distribution
不均一な財務分布
So it might be a good idea to tax the wealth and people
だから富と国民に課税するのは良い考えかもしれない
Another idea is to pay taxes
もう一つのアイデアは税金を支払うことです
small for tax
税金としては小さい
Our small class method of course has two methods
私たちの少人数クラスのメソッドには、もちろん 2 つのメソッドがあります。
One is like America
一つはアメリカのようなもの
only in the last stage
最後の段階だけ
tax when you spend
使ったときの税金
just consume
ただ消費するだけ
This is like Taiwan and the European Union
これは台湾と欧州連合のようなものです
we call it business value tax
私たちはそれを事業価値税と呼んでいます
for each stage
各ステージごとに
taxation of part of the value
価値の一部に対する課税
but we know your total value in the endgame
しかし、私たちはエンドゲームにおけるあなたの合計価値を知っています
Is it the same value as yours?
それはあなたと同じ価値観ですか？
So it is generally believed that
したがって、一般的には次のように考えられています
No matter you are in the United States, you are tracking
あなたが米国にいても、あなたは追跡しています
Sales Tax for Stage Courses
ステージコースの消費税
Or the so-called business value tax in the EU and Taiwan
または、EU と台湾のいわゆる事業価値税
Its main difference is that it is equal to
主な違いは、次と等しいことです。
It's right to add a difference in means
手段の差を加えるのが正しい
collect in one segment
1つのセグメントに集める
It's still the last stage to collect
まだ収集は最終段階です
less than two basically
基本的には2人未満
You can think of it like it's a consumption tax
消費税と同じように考えてください
sale tax
消費税
It is generally considered a regressive tax
一般的には逆進性のある税金と考えられています
So it's generally considered a bad tax
そのため、一般的には悪税とみなされています
right
右
it is a regressive tax
それは逆進税です
but this point of view
しかし、この視点
I don't think that's right
それは正しくないと思います
how to say
どのように言って
point in time to observe
観察する時点
is indeed
確かに
This is a regressive tax. Why is it a regressive tax?
これは逆進税ですが、なぜ逆進税なのでしょうか。
Because those who kept higher
上位を維持した人たちだから
Because if you consume it, you are done eating, right?
だって食べたら終わりですよね？
finished eating
食べ終えた
like eating
食べるのが好き
your stomach is that big
あなたのお腹はとても大きいです
you can't eat a lot
たくさん食べられない
There is probably a limit to how well you eat.
まともに食べるにも限界があるかもしれません。
For example, a rich person like Guo Taiming
たとえば、郭台銘のようなお金持ちの人は、
you eat well
あなたはよく食べます
Anyway, his defense is dozens or hundreds of times better than mine
とにかく彼の守備は私の何十倍、何百倍も優れています。
But he probably only eats mine
でも彼はおそらく私のものしか食べない
only my double or double
私の二重か二重だけ
he spent money
彼はお金を使った
Because this is a very real problem
これは非常に現実的な問題なので、
because you eat
あなたが食べるから
your stomach is that big
あなたのお腹はとても大きいです
So if we look at it from the perspective of a certain time period
つまり、ある一定の期間という観点から見ると、
He is indeed a regressive
彼はまさに退行者だ
Because of the consumption proportion of the master's starting hand
マスターの初手の消費割合のせいで
is relatively low
比較的低いです
Excluding the specific gravity is relatively high
比重を除くと比較的高い
Conversely, if you keep low
逆に、低くしておくと、
Like when I compare with Guo Taiming
郭台銘と比べたときのように
His removal rate must be much higher than mine
彼の除去率は私よりもはるかに高いはずです
I'm relatively low handed
私は比較的下手なほうです
When starting the consumption and removing the proportion
消費を開始し、割合を削除するとき
will
意思
In other words, consumption is higher
つまり消費量が増える
If I remove it, the proportion will be lower
外すと割合が下がります
But since GST is a proportional tax
しかし、GSTは比例税なので、
Consumption tax is a tax on consumption
消費税は消費にかかる税金です
There is no tax on the outgoing part
出金部分には税金はかかりません
Therefore, the proportion of consumption in the current income is relatively low
したがって、経常所得に占める消費の割合は相対的に低い。
He is a master
彼は達人です
Those who spend more than the current income will be lower-handed
現在の収入以上に消費する人は立場が下になる
Taxes that pay a relatively large proportion of income
収入の比較的大きな割合を占める税金
In other words, Porteimon, for example
つまり、例えばポルタイモン。
He earns hundreds of millions each
彼はそれぞれ何億も稼いでいます
His consumption may be, for example, 10 million
彼の消費額は、たとえば 1,000 万である可能性があります。
My income may be, say, 100,000
私の収入は例えば10万かもしれません
I spend maybe 50,000
たぶん5万くらい使ってる
Look at the proportion of the digger, he spends 10 million out of 100 million
採掘者の割合を見てください、彼は1億のうち1000万を費やしています
10 million is very high
1000万って結構高いよな
But compared to 100 million
でも1億に比べたら
just one tenth
ちょうど10分の1
But my words say 100,000
でも私の言葉では10万と言われています
When the spend reaches 60,000
支出が60,000に達したとき
I'm six out of ten
私は10中6です
So the proportion of my payment is obviously higher than that of buying Taiwan doors
つまり、私の支払いの割合は、台湾のドアを購入するよりも明らかに高いです
So most people think this tax is a bad tax
だからほとんどの人はこの税金は悪い税金だと思っている
it is a view on regressive taxation
それは逆進性課税に関する見解です
but let's think about it
でも考えてみましょう
People don't just live in a certain world, they live in a very long time
人は特定の世界にだけ生きているのではなく、非常に長い時間を生きています。
It's hard to say if you don't care about the Middle Ages
中世から気にしないと言うのは難しいです
How should I put it? First, if you compare at a certain point in time
なんというか、まずある時点で比較すると
When you start with a high score and a low score, it is probably related to your age
高いスコアと低いスコアから始まる場合、それはおそらく年齢に関連しています。
For example, if you think about it, when you first entered the workplace, your salary must not be high
例えば、考えてみれば、入社したての頃は給料も高くないはずです。
Conversely, when you retire, you have no salary at that time, so the lockup must be relatively low
逆に、退職するとその時点では給与がなくなるため、ロックアップは比較的低くなければなりません
Conversely, when you are in your fifties or sixties, your salary is at its peak
逆に50代、60代になると給料がピークになります。
So at that time, young people paid a higher proportion of consumption tax and consumption tax.
ですから、当時は若者のほうが消費税、消費税の負担率が高かったんですね。
Or the consumption tax paid by the elderly is relatively high, and the tax paid by people in their fifties and sixties will be relatively low
あるいは、高齢者の消費税は相対的に高く、50代、60代の消費税は相対的に安くなる
This is purely the number of years, purely the number of years
これは純粋に年数です、純粋に年数です
Because you are young and you will be fifty or sixty one day
あなたは若いから、いつかは50歳か60歳になるでしょう。
Fifty or sixty years old will retire one day
50歳か60歳の人はいつか引退するだろう
So this is the peak
ということでここがピークです
If you want to get up, be your own, so in other words
起き上がりたければ、自分のものになれ、つまり
A result of the different cycles of this life
この人生のさまざまなサイクルの結果
It's right to be a gap
ギャップがあるのが正しい
So at a certain point in time you watch this
つまり、ある時点でこれを視聴すると、
Observe with you from a person's life
人の人生をあなたと一緒に観察しましょう
This is different, you see
これは違います、わかりますか
What will you do with the money you earn in your life
人生で稼いだお金は何に使いますか
what will happen to you you will eventually run out
あなたはどうなりますか、最終的には使い果たされます
How should I put it, eat it and spend it if you want
なんというか、終わって過ごしてもいいですよ。
Either donate to your child
あなたの子供に寄付するか
or leave an inheritance to your children
もしくは子供たちに遺産を残すか
Just leave a legacy to donate this thing
これを寄付するには遺産を残してください
can be counted as an expense
経費として計上できる
words with some form of consumption
何らかの消費を伴う言葉
You just spend your money, right?
ただお金を使ってるだけですよね？
you are in the middle of your life
あなたは人生の真っ最中です
You're done eating again, right?
また食べ終わったんですよね？
But you might just pass the money on to your kids
でもそのお金を子供たちに渡すだけかもしれない
or bequeath to your children
または子供たちに遺贈する
But it would be nice to leave that bequest
でも遺言を残しておけばよかった
Or change hands
あるいは手を変えるか
see it as some kind of
それをある種のものとして見てください
Formal consumption, because a tax will be levied for a while
しばらく税金がかかるので正式消費
you see it as a form of consumption
あなたはそれを消費の一形態として見ています
I think it is more reasonable to say that this tax is basically a proportional tax
この税は基本的には比例税であると言ったほうが妥当だと思います。
Because the end of my middle hand is all spent?
中手の先が全部終わったから？
you see from a certain practice
ある実践からわかること
it is a tax refund
それは税金の還付です
If you look at it from the point of view of your life, what is the end of your life?
あなたの人生という観点から見た場合、あなたの人生の終わりは何ですか？
spend it in some form
何らかの形でそれを費やす
Speaking of those forms, we all regard it as some kind of consumption
そういった形態について言えば、私たちは皆、それをある種の消費だと考えています。
We will give it a lesson on that consumption
その消費について教訓を与えます
For example, consumption tax
例えば、消費税
For example, if we talk about the tax for a while, we will impose a proportional tax of 10%.
例えば、ちょっと税金の話をしますと、10％の比例税を課します。
At least now than consumption tax
少なくとも今は消費税よりは
The consumption tax rate is still high, because the consumption tax is now 5%
消費税が5％になったので、まだまだ消費税率が高いです
Because it's 5%, now
今は5%だから
It’s been 10% for a while, it’s even higher than that
一時は10%だったけど、それよりもさらに高い
So in a way
ある意味では
From the point of view of life, maybe it is not a person
人生という観点から見ると、それは人ではないかもしれません
not alone
一人じゃない
And in fact someone did a study
そして実際に誰かが研究をしました
It turns out that from a lifetime point of view
生涯の観点から見ると、
Maybe from a certain experiment, for example, this year
おそらく今年の、ある実験によるものでしょう。
it's really different
それは本当に違います
words from a lifelong point of view
生涯を見据えた言葉
Its discovery is that
その発見とは、
in fact a billy tax
実際には税金です
and it even has a D
そしてDも付いています
even a bump
たとえバンプでも
I don't want you to be rough, right?
乱暴なことはしてほしくないですよね？
it says even a little tired
少しでも疲れていると言います
I don't know what's the reason for this tiredness
この疲れの原因がわからない
But basically you can imagine
しかし、基本的には想像できます
From a lifetime perspective, this tax
生涯という観点から見ると、この税金は
I think billy tax is more reasonable
請求税の方が合理的だと思う
Billy tax is more reasonable
ビリー税のほうが合理的
In a certain experiment, the height of your hand is D
ある実験で手の高さはD
For example, like when I was just now
たとえば、さっきのような
When you are middle-aged, of course you earn more money
中年になれば当然収入は増える
when you were young
あなたが若い時
Of course, when you are old, you earn less money
当然、高齢になれば収入は減ります
So from this point of view
したがって、この観点からすると
The tax you pay is higher
納める税金のほうが高いよ
So the tax will be lower
それで税金も安くなる
Because you spend less
支出の割合が比較的低いため
more when you were young
もっと若い頃は
spend more money
もっとお金を使う
So the tax is heavier
だから税金も重くなるんだよ
This is purely a matter of age
これは純粋に年齢の問題です
words from a lifelong point of view
生涯を見据えた言葉
i think it should be a billy tax
税金を課すべきだと思う
This is what I want to emphasize
これが私が強調したいことです
may be
多分
Talk to us about consumption tax in general
消費税全般についてご相談ください
Generally the strongest objection is that
一般的に最も強い反対意見は、
it is a tax refund
それは税金の還付です
at least i don't think so
少なくとも私はそうは思わない
I think it should be a more reasonable view
もっと合理的な見方をすべきだと思う
from a lifelong perspective
生涯的な観点から
You keep it all your life and spend it all in the end
あなたはそれを一生守り続け、最後にはすべてを費やします
And I will give you a certain percentage if I spend all of it
全額使ったら一定の割合をあげます
it is a proportional tax
それは比例税です
if so
もしそうなら
Then there is another view as we said earlier
それから、先ほども言ったように別の見方もあります
That is to say, there are probably many of us
つまり、おそらく私たちの多くは
probably all
おそらく全部
That is, many of the taxes paid are payroll taxes.
つまり、支払われる税金の多くは給与税です。
salary
給料
So here we have a profile
それではプロフィールをご紹介します
have a profile
プロフィールがある
That is to say, with the past two years
つまり、この2年間で
Two years of tax returns
2年間の納税申告書
The salary is about
給料は約
On our tax return it's about 75%
私たちの納税申告書では約 75% です
That is to say, in our tax filing
つまり、私たちの税務申告では、
belonging to the payroll
給与に属する
Based on the data of the past two years
過去2年間のデータをもとに
on average
平均して
average about
平均的に約
This should be a photo
これは写真になるはずです
Hundreds of billions
数千億
More than three trillion, that's probably, the mental part,
3兆以上、それはおそらく精神的な部分です、
In other words, about 15% of the mind part of our New Year's materials
言い換えれば、新年の教材のマインドの部分の約 15%
The non-mental part is about one trillion,
非精神的な部分は約1兆、
In other words, the three trillion and one trillion account for about 25%
つまり、3兆と1兆で約25％を占めます。
If we compare this information with the United States,
この情報を米国と比較すると、
Compared with other European countries,
他のヨーロッパ諸国と比べて、
How about it? In the United States, if we also use the data of the past two years to look at it,
どうでしょうか、アメリカでも過去2年間のデータで見てみると、
The ratio of its mind to movement is about 56.3,
精神と運動の比率は約56.3で、
In other words, less than 60%
つまり60％未満
About 43% after non-psychological ratio
精神疾患以外の割合 約43％
If we look at the OECD countries in Europe,
ヨーロッパのOECD加盟国に目を向けてみると、
Using the data of the past two years for comparison,
過去2年間のデータを比較してみると、
It's even lower than this,
これよりもさらに低いのですが、
less than, in other words, half and half,
言い換えれば、半分未満、
In other words, on the information about the age,
つまり、ハグ年齢の素材上、
data presented in other countries,
他国で発表されたデータ、
My thoughts are not so high,
私の考えはそれほど高いものではありませんが、
However, the ratio shown in our Taiwan data is quite high,
ただし、台湾のデータで示されている比率は非常に高く、
about 75%,
約75%、
If you compare it with the United States,
アメリカと比べてみると、
Can you see it or not?
見えるか見えないか？
For example, if you think of it as sixty-four
例えば64歳と考えると
This is about half and half
これは半分半分くらいです
But Taiwan's words seventy-five-eight
しかし、台湾の言葉は七五八
what is this manifestation
この現象は何ですか
means that part of our non-new place
それは私たちの新しい場所の一部を意味します
probably a lot
おそらくたくさん
Probably didn't get it
おそらく理解できなかった
Then what is a primary idea
そして、基本的なアイデアは何ですか
The primary idea is that we know
基本的な考え方は、私たちは知っているということです
what you earn is your income
あなたが稼いだものがあなたの収入です
Another time you will spend
あなたが過ごすもう一つの時間
This is your consumer side
これは消費者側です
I just said the words spent
私はただ費やした言葉を言っただけです
you think of it as a generalized flower
あなたはそれを一般化された花だと考えています
For example, the inheritance you leave to your children
たとえば、子供たちに残す遺産。
You end up spending it too
結局あなたもそれを費やすことになります
Here we have an income tax
ここに所得税があります
Here we have an excise tax or business value tax
ここには消費税または事業価値税があります
in other words
言い換えると
Income side of your income
収入の収入面
I carve an income tax
所得税を刻みます
on the side of where you get paid
お金をもらう側で
I engrave a GST
GSTを刻印します
Taiwan called business value tax
台湾は事業価値税と呼ぶ
If we don't have a good grasp of this aspect of keeping
維持のこの側面を十分に理解していないと、
From the data point of view, it is not well grasped
データの観点からは十分に把握されていない
Can we start from the side of consumption
消費の側から始められないか
cover him partly
彼を部分的に覆う
And this side feels like Shinnomori's stand is busy and high
そしてこちら側は新ノ森のスタンドが忙しくて高い気がする
So this guard is probably as you can imagine
したがって、このガードはおそらくご想像どおりです
Mostly you can think of him as a new tax guard
ほとんどの場合、彼は新しい税務職員だと考えてよいでしょう
Therefore, there may be a gap in Taiwan's tax compliance.
したがって、台湾の税務コンプライアンスにはギャップがある可能性があります。
He still has 25% he is not a non-new guard
彼はまだ 25% を持っています、彼は新人ではありません
Roughly you can imagine that it mainly comes from Shinnoshu
おおよそ神農州が主であることが想像できます。
But on the other hand, consumption tax
しかしその一方で、消費税は
So a basic idea is to say
基本的な考え方は次のとおりです
You missed the tax on this side
こちら側の税金を見逃しています
But when you spend you still spend
しかし、お金を使うときはまだお金を使います
So guarding this missing part I didn't engrave it
だから欠けた部分を守って彫らなかった
can i spend time from you
あなたから時間をかけてもいいですか？
I cover you back
私はあなたを守ります
because you're guarding this side now
あなたがこれを守っているから
Basically this new information guards the tax
基本的に、この新しい情報は税金を守るものです
There are a lot of guards missing
行方不明の警備員がたくさんいる
That is to say, there are structural problems
つまり構造的な問題がある
There are so many holes in the chamber
チャンバーには穴がたくさんある
open economy again
再び開放経済
so your class that tax is a bit difficult
それであなたのクラスは税金が少し難しいです
But you still have to spend it if you want to eat it hot
しかし、温かいものを食べたい場合は、それでもお金を費やす必要があります
so spend this part
だからこの部分を費やしてください
This aspect is equal to your taxes, for example,
この側面は税金に相当します。たとえば、
If you have raised it here, for example, within 1,000 yuan
ここで例えば1,000元以内に上げた場合
You only go up to say 700 yuan
700元までしか上がらない
You missed 300 yuan
300元を逃しました
But it still has to spend out of the 1000
しかし、それでも 1000 のうちの 1 つを費やさなければなりません
here when it's spent
使い終わったらここで
can i raise it back
上げ直してもいいですか
and it feels like
そしてそれはそうなるような気がします
Here you have raised to 7000 yuan
これで7000元まで集まりました
but on this side
でもこちら側では
you may be 1000 yuan
1000元かもしれない
your tax is bigger
あなたの税金の方が大きいです
So the basic idea is to say
基本的な考え方は次のとおりです
can i get it back from the other side
向こうから取り返してもらえますか
get it back like this
このように返してください
This is probably my most basic idea
おそらくこれが私の最も基本的な考えです
the idea
このアイデア
you look first
あなたが最初に見てください
As long as the so-called tax is the new tax
いわゆる税金が新しい税金である限り
If your salary is taxable, if your salary is taxable
あなたの給与が課税対象の場合、あなたの給与が課税対象の場合
What is the gap between you and your sales tax?
あなたと消費税の間のギャップはどこにありますか?
The difference is that if you have accumulated financial resources now,
違いは、もしあなたが今財政力を蓄えているなら、
If you accumulate finances, for example, if you have several houses,
資金を蓄積すると、たとえば家をいくつか持っている場合、
Keeping the tax is not a lesson to us,
税金を守り続けることは私たちにとって教訓ではありません、
Because it's basically a payroll tax,
基本的には給与税なので、
In other words, if we determine that Taiwan's Shou De tax,
つまり、台湾の寿徳税を決定すると、
Basically, if a new capital keeps tax,
基本的に、新しい資本が税金を維持する場合、
Your wealth need not be taxed,
あなたの富に課税する必要はありません。
You don't have to keep the tax, it's right, you can't pay the tax, it's right,
税金は納めなくていい、そうだ、税金は払えない、そうだ、
But if you turn it into sales tax, I can get it,
でもそれを消費税に換算すればもらえるよ
Why can I attend class?
なぜ授業に参加できるのですか？
Because sooner or later all your life will be spent,
遅かれ早かれあなたの人生はすべて費やされるから、
So we will also send out in this house
なのでこの家でも発信していきます
How to send it away?
どうやって送り出すのですか？
He might just sell it or leave it to his son
彼はそれを売るか息子に残すかもしれない
but anyway
とにかく
For those corners, we consider him to be a kind of consumption
それらのコーナーでは、私たちは彼を一種の消費者だと考えています
From the consumption fee, we can still keep it from flying
消費料からすればまだ飛ばさないようにできる
So this is payroll tax versus excise tax
つまり、これは給与税と消費税です
I think one of the biggest differences
最大の違いの一つだと思います
In other words, if you use the payroll tax
つまり、給与税を使うと
In other words, what tax do you pay?
言い換えれば、あなたはどのような税金を払っていますか？
You have to pay taxes when you work at a young age
若いうちから働くと税金を払わなければならない
wait till old age
老後まで待つ
You don’t have to pay for every few accounts
いくつかのアカウントごとに支払う必要はありません
because hand tax
手税のせいで
Pay as we just said
先ほど言ったように支払います
It's basically a payroll tax
基本的には給与税です
you were making money when you were young
あなたは若い頃お金を稼いでいました
You have to pay this tax on the money you earn
あなたは稼いだお金に対してこの税金を支払わなければなりません
But you don't have to pay every few financial
しかし、数回ごとに金銭を支払う必要はありません
On the contrary, if you pay consumption tax
逆に消費税を払うと
what kind of personality does it have
どのような性格を持っていますか
Because consumption tax means
消費税ということですから、
You have to pay for what you consume
消費した分は支払わなければなりません
If I just imagine
ただ想像してみると
Say you leave a house for your son
息子のために家を出たとします
It's also a form of consumption
それも一種の消費です
That consumption tax can be taught
消費税は教えられること
But the tax of the workshop is not covered
ただしワークショップの税金は対象外です
And here I have quoted this article
そして、こちらの記事を引用させていただきました
he has an opinion
彼には意見がある
It is said that wealth is not equal to the wealth of a society
富は社会の富と同じではないと言われています
uneven words
不均等な言葉
Consumption tax is better than lock tax
ロック税より消費税の方が良い
Why? Because wealth is uneven
なぜでしょうか? 富が不均一だからです
Your locked tax payment is basically a new lock tax
あなたのロックされた税金の支払いは基本的に新しいロック税です
Wealth is tantamount to being useless
富は役に立たないのと同じだ
unless you like what we said earlier
先ほど言ったことが気に入らない限り
can a property tax
固定資産税はかかりますか
Property tax is of course more direct
もちろん固定資産税のほうが直接的です
But if the property tax cannot be paid
ただし、固定資産税が支払えない場合
Consumption tax is tantamount to indirect eight-and-a-half guide
消費税は間接八分半に等しい
because when you want to consume
なぜなら、消費したいときは
For example, you may sell your house to make a consumption
たとえば、消費のために家を売るかもしれません。
bequeath that house to your son
その家をあなたの息子に遺贈してください
If we regard all these as a consumption
これらすべてを消費として捉えると
And we do make these things on the tax system
そして私たちはこれらのことを税制に基づいて行っています
We all have words for it
私たちは皆、それにふさわしい言葉を持っています
Excise taxes are actually better improvements than locked-in taxes
物品税は実際には固定された税よりも優れた改善策である
Lock separation Financial separation
ロックの分離 経済的な分離
because of the wealth of those ages
あの時代の豊かさのせいで
You can't pay the tax for the new lock
新しいロックの税金を支払うことはできません
Because you only get this tax when you are in the new lock
なぜなら、この税金を受け取ることができるのは、新しいロックに入っているときだけだからです。
But consumption tax can be imposed
ただし消費税は課税される可能性がある
Why?
なぜ？
because of your finances
あなたの財政のせいで
In the end it will be spent in some form
結局は何らかの形で使われることになる
Like leaving an inheritance to your son
息子に遺産を残すようなもの
or will spend in some form
あるいは何らかの形で支出する
once spent
一度過ごした
If we interpret it as an expense in a relatively broad sense
比較的広い意味での経費として解釈すると
Consumption tax can be taxed to this tax
この税金には消費税が課税される可能性があります
class to this tax
この税金のクラス
and he thinks
そして彼はこう思う
If a society's finances are uneven
社会の財政が不均衡であれば
GST is a better tax
GSTはより良い税金です
right
右
because of the financial part
金銭的な部分のせいで
Sales tax is available
消費税が利用可能です
Where's your tax?
あなたの税金はどこにありますか？
If it is a salary hand tax
給与手税なら
If it belongs to the tax nature of salary hand
給与ハンドの税性に属する場合
Less than this class
このクラス未満
So my idea is to say
そこで私の考えはこう言います
we are small now
私たちは今小さいです
If we are now in Taiwan
もし私たちが今台湾にいるとしたら
In Taiwan, it is business
台湾ではビジネスです
Business value is now 5%
ビジネス価値は 5% になりました
5%
５％
Then my idea is to say
そこで私の考えはこう言うことです
Because my property tax is used to make up for the lack of helper's tax
ヘルパー税の不足を補うために私の固定資産税が使われているからです
Because the property is there
物件があるから
This person has accumulated
この人は積み上げてきた
After the accumulation is over, it is like the land
蓄積が終わったら、それは土地のようだ
right there
すぐそこに
over there words
そこの言葉
if you pay taxes again
また税金を払ったら
From the point of view of education
教育という観点から見ると
no efficiency loss
効率の損失なし
because he has accumulated
彼は積み上げてきたから
before you accumulate
貯まる前に
he will affect that is to say
彼は影響を与えるだろう、つまり
Do I want to accumulate
貯めたいですか
For example, you now announce that
たとえば、今次のように発表しました。
I am now for his property
私は今彼の財産のためにいます
I have to pay heavier taxes
もっと重い税金を支払わなければならない
what will he affect
彼は何に影響を与えるだろうか
Affect those who have not yet accumulated
まだ蓄積していない人に影響を与える
or those who want to accumulate
または積み立てたい方
for those who have accumulated
積み上げてきた人たちのために
he was not
彼はそうではなかった
fully manageable
完全に管理可能
Because once the government announces
政府が発表したら
For example, for each household, I now add it to the moderator of the middle school
例えば、各家庭ごとに、中学校の司会者に追加するようになりました。
it has a phenomenon
それは現象があります
This is what we call capitalization
これが大文字化と呼ばれるものです
What is capitalization?
大文字化とは何ですか?
What is the value of your house
あなたの家にはどのくらいの価値がありますか
The value of a house is
家の価値というのは、
You can generate income in the future
将来的に収入を得ることができる
This income includes the income you live in
この収入には居住地の収入も含まれます
Also includes the proceeds that you can rent out
レンタルできる収益も含まれます
This is what this house is worth
これがこの家の価値です
you live alone
あなたは一人暮らしです
Or you can rent it out to someone else
あるいは他の人に貸すこともできます
you can collect this income
あなたはこの収入を受け取ることができます
Think about it, once the government collects taxes
考えてみてください、政府が税金を徴収したら
what does it mean
どういう意味ですか
means, for example, that every month you
たとえば、毎月、
Originally, the rent could have been, say, 20,000 yuan.
当初の家賃は例えば2万元だったかもしれない。
I can take a class now
これで授業を受けられるようになりました
It's like a little bit of 20,000 yuan
2万円ちょっとですかね
The government took 5,000 yuan
政府は5000元を受け取った
what is this wish
この願いは何ですか
You could have rented your house at 20,000 yuan a month
あなたは月2万元で家を借りることができただろう
Once the government announces that
政府がそれを発表したら、
Out of the 20,000, I can collect 5,000.
20,000個のうち5,000個は集められます。
including real estate
不動産も含めて
It means that the value of each root of your house is only 15,000
つまり、あなたの家の各根の価値はわずか15,000です
15,000 for each 15,000 if you fly it back
飛行機で戻る場合は、15,000 回につき 15,000 円
The value of this section of the house will drop immediately
家のこの部分の価値はすぐに下がります
we fall
私たちは落ちる
This is the capitalization of our education
これが私たちの教育の資本化です
capitalization
大文字化
So this poor means
つまり、この貧しいということは、
ok
Ok
what we say
私たちが言うこと
that is
あれは
right now
たった今
That is to say, directly tax the finances
つまり、財政に直接課税するということです。
Of course it is a better way
もちろんその方が良い方法です
but if not
しかし、そうでない場合は
we can retire as a planner
プランナーとして引退してもいい
Make a correction from the consumption tax
消費税からの補正を行います
Of course our current consumption tax rate is 5%
もちろん現在の消費税率は5%です
The tax rate of hand tax is of course much higher
もちろん手税の税率はもっと高いです
so how to correct
それで、どうやって修正するか
One of my thoughts is to say
私の考えの一つはこう言うことです
Is it possible to treat all consumer goods as
すべての消費財を次のように扱うことは可能でしょうか?
Two-level cargo industry
二層貨物産業
one is normal
1つは正常です
One is a high-end product like this
一つはこんな高級品
Let's give it five boards for the blue bottle
青いボトルのためにボードを 5 枚あげましょう
For high-end bottles, we will give them a relatively high breakage rate, and the board will be ten.
ハイエンドボトルの場合は比較的高い破損率を与え、ボードは10になります。
At present, we want to talk about the provisions of the business tax law
今回は事業税法の規定についてお話したいと思います。
The applicable tax rate for the business tax rate is the lowest board, the board with the highest five boards
事業税率の適用税率は、最も低い板、最も高い板から5つの板が適用されます。
There is administrative luck in this tax increase
今回の増税には行政の幸運がある
In case you want to mention board five, just prove
ボード 5 について言及したい場合は、証明してください。
I declared to myself that if I want class five, I don’t have to go through the Legislative Yuan.
私は、5 級が欲しければ立法院を通過する必要はない、と自分に宣言しました。
What I'm breaking down here is to say
私がここで言いたいのは、
Is it possible to divide our consumer products into two categories
当社の消費者製品を 2 つのカテゴリーに分けることはできますか?
One is more commonly used
1 つはより一般的に使用される
One is a relatively high-end bottle
1つは比較的高級なボトルです
Can be divided into two categories
2つのカテゴリに分類できます
So the basic idea is something like
基本的な考え方は次のようなものです
Is it necessary to expand the current facility tax to a relatively large extent?
現在の施設税を比較的大幅に拡大する必要があるのか​​。
This is probably the most basic idea
おそらくこれが最も基本的な考え方です
So the overall source
つまり全体的なソースは
I'd say it's probably the first
おそらくそれが最初だと思います
It is very problematic on the tax of the hand
手の税金に関しては非常に問題があります
Not as good as we thought
思ったほど良くない
from the tax system
税制から
Let's see, from the competition plan
コンペ計画から見てみましょう
Feeling, of course, is full of problems
気持ちはもちろん問題だらけ
So since there is a problem
それで問題があるので
So in terms of the design of Suizhi
さて、Suizhi のデザインに関して言えば、
We're going to have a whole new, different idea
私たちはまったく新しい、異なるアイデアを思いつくつもりです
And the question I think
そして私が思う質問は
It's not that any one person can solve the problem
誰でも問題を解決できるわけではない
it's a structural problem
それは構造的な問題です
Because there are so many Chinese series in Taiwan
台湾には中華シリーズがたくさんあるので
those people are amazing
あの人たちはすごいです
You have to tax some people in Taiwan
台湾の一部の人々に税金を課さなければなりません
not so easy
そう簡単ではない
it's a structural problem
それは構造的な問題です
It's not that the government doesn't work hard
政府が頑張ってないわけではない
effort or not
努力か否か
like the words in the American data
アメリカのデータにある言葉のように
Sale Importment
販売輸入
It ran away with 57 out of 100
100点中57点で逃げ切った
America should be a very advanced country
アメリカは非常に先進的な国であるべきだ
Although it is the whole world to find
見つけるのは全世界だとしても
You are a U.S. citizen in Taiwan
あなたは台湾に居住する米国国民です
you have to pay taxes
あなたは税金を支払わなければなりません
it's pretty awesome
かなりすごいです
Look at the 100 yuan
100元を見てください
57 yuan escaped
57元逃げた
It means that this matter is not so easy to solve
つまり、この問題はそう簡単に解決できないということだ
Taiwan is another open economy
台湾もまた開放経済です
in the words of master
マスターの言葉で
flow fast
速く流れる
Those who are very high should have a lower tax rate
高額所得者は税率を下げる必要がある
From the point of view of education
教育という観点から見ると
From the point of view of efficiency, it should be low and should not be high
効率の観点から、それは低くなければならず、高くすべきではありません
It's not so easy when you tax him
彼に税金を課すのはそう簡単ではない
So the tax at hand, judging from the data, is there any problem
データから判断すると、現在の税金に問題はありますか?
From a structural point of view, it is not so easy to correct him.
構造的な観点から言えば、彼を矯正するのはそう簡単ではありません。
So for an idea that arises is to say
そこで、思いついたアイデアについては、次のようになります。
Taiwan's tax structure may have a very different idea
台湾の税制の考え方は大きく異なる可能性がある
Can not follow our general academic qualifications
一般的な学歴に従えない
That is, the idea you read in the textbook
つまり、教科書で読んだ考え方です
to design the tax system
税制を設計する
rather than a fair dispute
公正な論争ではなく
How about I have to tax the masters heavily?
マスターたちに重税を課すのはどうだろうか？
But maybe when actually executing
しかし、おそらく実際に実行するときは
have a big problem
大きな問題がある
I'm just saying today
今日だけ言っておきます
Is it possible to look at it from two perspectives
二つの視点から見ることは可能でしょうか
from property tax
固定資産税から
It's certainly a nice tax system
確かにありがたい税制ですね
he has accumulated over there
彼はあそこに積み上げてきた
And wealth inequality is a problem for workers in Greater Asia
そして富の不平等は大アジアの労働者にとって問題となっている
If you tax him the stuff accumulated over there
そこに蓄積されたものに彼に税金を課したら
no efficiency loss
効率の損失なし
His loss of efficiency is
彼の効率の低下は、
those of the future who are ready to accumulate
蓄積する準備ができている未来の人たち
Because he thought of the tax in the class
授業中に税金のことを考えたので
I don't want to accumulate
溜めたくない
I accumulate less
貯まる量が減りました
will affect
影響するだろう
but for the accumulated
しかし、蓄積されたものに対して
In other words, how many houses do you have now those people
言い換えれば、その人たちは今何軒の家を持っていますか？
There is actually nothing to lose
実は失うものは何もない
like a piece of land
まるで土地のように
you put there first
あなたが最初にそこに置きました
I give you lessons
私はあなたにレッスンを与えます
No matter how high the tax is, you have nothing to do
税金がいくら高くても何もすることはない
It's not like saying you're a master of taxation
税金の達人だなんて言うのとは違いますよ
He moves the finances out
彼は資金を外に移す
He removes all that he gets
彼は得たものをすべて取り除く
This will affect the behavior
これは動作に影響します
you accumulate over there first
あなたは最初にそこに蓄積します
I will tax you even higher
もっと高い税金をあげます
It won't affect your behavior
あなたの行動には影響しません
it's a property tax
それは固定資産税です
another excise tax
別の消費税
consumption tax
消費税の話です
He should not be a tax burden
彼は税金の負担になるべきではない
From a lifelong perspective
生涯にわたる視点から
you make a definition of consumption
消費の定義を決めるのはあなたです
to give a broad explanation
大まかな説明をする
I think it's more reasonable
そのほうが合理的だと思う
because he should be a tax
彼は税金であるべきだから
than tax
税金よりも
while consumption tax
一方で消費税
Compared with the tax compliance based on the new capital tax compliance
新資本税対応に基づく税務対応との比較
he has an advantage
彼には利点がある
It's your annual financial part.
それはあなたの毎年の財務上の部分です
He can't pay tax on salary
彼は給料に税金を払うことができない
GST can be paid by him
GSTは彼が支払うことができます
Because sooner or later those finances of yours are going to be spent in some form
遅かれ早かれあなたの資金は何らかの形で使われることになるからです
Once spent, he has some form of consumption
一度支出すると、何らかの形で消費することになる
once a form of consumption
かつては消費の一形態であった
Consumption tax has a way to tax this tax
消費税にはこの税金を課税する方法があります
For a country, as long as the financial distribution becomes more unequal,
国家にとって、財政分配がさらに不平等になる限り、
Excise tax is actually better than hand tax
消費税は実際には手税よりも良い
But consumption tax we know that the current tax rate is 5% which is low
しかし、消費税は現在の税率が5％であることは知っていますが、これは低いです。
You're going to replace the tax on hands with the GST
手元にある税金を GST に置き換えるつもりです
I don't think it's that easy
そんなに簡単ではないと思います
So a possible solution
したがって、考えられる解決策としては
I think it is possible to divide our consumption into two commodities
私たちの消費は 2 つの商品に分けることができると思います
One is probably more normal
1つはおそらくもっと普通です
One is more advanced
1つはより高度です
We give it two tax rates
2 つの税率を適用します
Of course, there are many problems in practice and operation.
もちろん、実践や運用には多くの問題があります。
For example, if you do this
たとえば、これを行うと
Do many people buy through online shopping?
ネットショッピングで購入する人も多いのでしょうか？
or export to buy
または輸出して購入する
Of course, there are very real issues to consider.
もちろん、考慮すべき非常に現実的な問題があります。
very real problem
非常に現実的な問題
It's the opposite of paying
支払うのとは逆です
OK, I'll probably stop here today
はい、今日はここでやめようと思います
we have a little time now to ask questions
質問する時間が少しあります
bring it up with me please cut it short
それを私に持ち出してください、短くしてください
Thank you teacher for your wonderful speech
先生、素晴らしいスピーチをありがとうございました
What I want to ask is also for the two very brilliant ideas you just mentioned
私が聞きたいのは、あなたが今言及した 2 つの非常に素晴らしいアイデアについてです。
First property tax
初めての固定資産税
Taiwan has the mutual characteristics of small and medium-sized enterprises
台湾は中小企業の共通の特徴を持っています
The small and medium-sized enterprises serve each other and provide labor services to each other.
中小企業は相互にサービスを提供し、労働サービスを提供し合っています。
We can't grasp his little sorrow
私たちは彼の小さな悲しみを理解できない
On the other hand, you just mentioned
一方で、先ほどもおっしゃいましたが、
Accumulating wealth is ugly for a person's life
富を蓄積することは人の人生にとって醜いことである
Should be a good tax system too
税制も充実すればいいのに
But if I am the host of a small and medium-sized enterprise
でも私が中小企業のホストだったら
I've been accumulating my fortune in my own business
私は自分のビジネスで富を築いてきました
I don't want to accumulate on me
自分に蓄積したくない
I let my family continue to run the business
家族に事業を続けさせます
The property has always been enjoyed by the family
いつも家族で楽しまれている物件です
For this part, since he let the legal person accumulate the property
この部分については、法人に財産を蓄積させているので、
He has no other property of his own
彼は他に自分の財産を持っていない
to enjoy consumption
消費を楽しむために
Seems to be uncommon to the property tax
固定資産税は珍しいようです
Or the appearance of the consumption room
あるいは消費室の様子
I maybe you think
たぶんあなたはそう思うでしょう
no matter what
何があっても
Ask the teacher to tell you your information
先生にあなたの情報を教えてもらいます
this detail may
この詳細は
I can't say much
多くは言えません
This is equivalent to
これは以下と同等です
equal to a question on the executive side
経営陣側の質問に等しい
but what you just said
でもあなたが今言ったこと
I guess we should have rules
規制を設けるべきだと思う
You said what you said should be
あなたは言うべきことを言いました
Similar to the concept of retaining the cloud forest
雲霧林を維持するという概念に類似
like the money he made
彼が稼いだお金のように
He continued to accumulate in the company
彼は会社に蓄積し続けた
then my understanding
それから私の理解
Taiwan seems to have regulations on the preservation of Yunlin
台湾には雲林の保存に関する規制があるようです
There is a rule that says
というルールがあります
For example, if you accumulate to a certain extent
例えば、ある程度貯まると、
he's going to pay a tax or something
彼は税金か何かを支払うつもりだ
is that he should have one
彼はそれを持っているべきだということです
tantamount to having a
持っているのと同じ
There should be a relevant provision in this tax law
この税法に関連する規定があるはずです
it's impossible to say
言うことは不可能です
Then you say to keep all the money in the company
それからあなたはお金をすべて会社に保管すると言います
continue
続く
I understand this should
これは理解しています
should mean
意味するはずです
There are relevant provisions in the law
法律に関連規定がある
That probably belongs to Reserve Yunlin
それはおそらく雲林保護区のものでしょう
he may force you to assign
彼はあなたに割り当てを強制するかもしれない
or how
あるいはどうやって
or if you keep Yunlin too much
または雲林を維持しすぎると
he might be able to take a class
彼は授業を受けられるかもしれない
There's a retainer and there's a hundred-day tax
家臣がいて百日税がある
hundred days tax
百日税
So the previous industry you mentioned in the China region
先ほどおっしゃった業界は中国地域にあるということですね
how are each other
お互い元気ですか
I'm not so clear about this
これについてはよくわかりません
But he only needs to consume
しかし、彼は消費するだけで十分です
If he just goes shopping
彼がただ買い物に行くだけなら
if you buy something
何かを買うなら
He pays that tax
彼はその税金を払っています
Didn't he say for example
たとえば彼はこう言いませんでしたか？
previous hotel
前のホテル
just post what
何を投稿するだけ
He has to pay that tax, doesn't he?
彼はその税金を支払わなければなりませんね。
that's a question of performance
それはパフォーマンスの問題です
You just
あなたはただ
just consume
ただ消費するだけ
just like us
ちょうど私たちのような
As long as you spend, you have to pay that tax
お金を使う限り、その税金を支払わなければなりません
i guess your question
あなたの質問だと思います
should
したほうがいい
I have a hunch that it should be fine.
きっと大丈夫だろうという予感がする。
should be fine
大丈夫なはずです
but maybe some
でも多分一部は
That is to say I just came up with an idea
つまり、ただアイデアを思いついただけなんです
My basic idea is to say
私の基本的な考えはこう言います
first flick tax
最初のフリック税
Maybe not as good as expected
期待したほど良くないかもしれない
not as good as expected
期待したほど良くない
Since it is not as good as imagined
想像していたほど良くないので
what is the reason
理由は何ですか
I feel like a
のような気がします
structural problems
構造的な問題
not that you try to
あなたがしようとするわけではありません
What is he trying to change
彼は何を変えようとしているのか
I don't think it's
そうは思わない
not this question
この質問ではありません
In this case
この場合
I pay alone
私は一人で支払います
Maybe considering Taiwan's broken intelligence design
おそらく台湾の壊れた諜報設計を考慮しているのでしょう
call a new and different idea
新しくて違うアイデアを呼び出す
I just said not long ago
ついこの前も言ったばかりだ
We have a colleague who said this
こんなことを言った同僚がいます
he said in japan there is a debris room
彼は日本には瓦礫の部屋があると言った
i don't know what their name is
彼らの名前が何なのか分かりません
debris room
碎物室
his idea is to say
彼の考えはこう言うことだ
Each debris room, for example
たとえば各瓦礫部屋
Responsible for 100 SMEs
中小企業100社を担当
For example, it would be right to only manage 100 companies.
たとえば、100社だけを経営するのは正しいことです。
if you can imagine
想像できれば
I'm in charge of the debris room
私はゴミ部屋の担当です
For example, if there are 100 companies, I will be in charge.
例えば100社あったら私が担当します。
Maybe you can draw some bonuses
もしかしたらボーナスを引くことができるかもしれません
For example, I found
たとえば、私が見つけたのは、
how old should you be
何歳になったらいいですか
In the end you didn't speak
結局君は話さなかった
I can draw some bonuses
いくつかのボーナスを引くことができます
inject strength
力を注入する
i really want
本当に欲しい
Can't do well in Taiwan
台湾ではうまくいかない
For example, when we were young, we were so rich and strong
たとえば、私たちが若かった頃、私たちはとても裕福で強かった
that family is too famous
その家族はあまりにも有名です
i won't talk to my wife
妻とは話さない
I'll just drive there
そこに車で行くだけです
Fu Hang Dou Jiang
フー・ハン・ドゥ・ジャン
long time no go
お久しぶりです
I want to say, of course you can, line up for people to come.
私が言いたいのは、もちろん、人が来るまで並んでもいいということです。
Hehehe, let me tell him, forget it
ふふふ、言っておきます、忘れてください
So that's so famous, so famous
それはとても有名です、とても有名です
Think about it, maybe we can provide it
考えてみてください、私たちが提供できるかも知れません
That is, which one do you think can make a lot of money?
つまり、どちらが多くのお金を稼ぐことができると思いますか？
Maybe you check everyone
もしかしたらみんなチェックしてるかもしれない
Everyone is going to be a baking cup
みんながベーキングカップになるよ
go look it up go look it up he said
調べてみろ、調べてみろと彼は言った
If you find out, for example, you can get a commission before the lecture
たとえば、講演前にコミッションを得ることができれば、
For example, I don't know when I was a child
たとえば、私が子供の頃だったかは分かりませんが、
Will it? There may be a problem with this, that is,
これには問題があるかもしれません。
Will there be any missing complaints? Into the insult experiment
漏れはあるだろうか? 陵辱実験へ
He just gives it to you, to you, to you, which is a bit of a mess
彼はただあなたに、あなたに、あなたにそれを与えるだけですが、それはちょっと混乱です
Then, for example, your family, I will
それから、例えばあなたの家族、私はそうします
Anyway, seeing that you are very upset, I will report it to you.
とにかく、あなたがとても動揺しているのを見て、私はあなたにそれを報告します。
I said this family has tax evasion.
この家族は脱税していると言いました。
This has a related problem
これには関連する問題があります
But in terms of self-service design, it means
しかし、セルフサービス設計の観点から見ると、これは次のことを意味します。
For example, say something like this, for example, let
たとえば、次のように言います。
Everyone knows that, for example, there are a few that are not bad.
たとえば、悪くないものもいくつかあることは誰もが知っています。
This information can probably be grasped by adopting the purpose
この情報はおそらく目的を採用することで把握できるでしょう。
He can, because the Ministry of Finance is in the office, and he doesn't know
財務省がオフィスにいるのに、彼はそれを知らないからだ。
For example, if you compare several companies to make more money, the locals are probably small.
例えば、もっと儲かろうと複数の会社を比較した場合、地元の人は少ないでしょう。
I mean maybe some, either the basic idea or the
つまり、基本的なアイデアか、
That is to say, a problem like this may require a very different idea to solve it
つまり、このような問題を解決するには、まったく異なるアイデアが必要になる可能性があります。
Not like the traditional thinking, the traditional thinking
伝統的な考え方とは違う、伝統的な考え方
Because this problem I think is a structural problem
この問題は構造的な問題だと思うので
It's not a matter of working hard or not
頑張るか頑張らないかの問題ではない
Like the American words I just said, one hundred yuan, fifty-seven yuan escaped
さっき言ったアメリカ人の言葉のように、百元、五十七元が逃げた。
Like the US, it should be very strict.
米国のように、非常に厳しくする必要がある。
So my basic idea is that maybe what I just mentioned is just a possible direction
したがって、私の基本的な考えは、おそらく私が今述べたことは単なる可能性のある方向性であるということです
But maybe if you think about it, maybe it means
でも、もしかしたら考えてみたら、それはつまり、
It means that you can put forward different ideas and different views
つまり、さまざまなアイデアや見解を提案できるということです
There is a common saying in Taiwan
台湾にはこんな諺があります
So long live Taiwan
台湾万歳
So I ask Professor Yang to address this issue
そこで、ヤン教授にこの問題に取り組んでもらいたいと思います。
your opinion
あなたの意見
Is it true that there are many inappropriate taxes in Taiwan?
台湾には不適切な税金が多いというのは本当ですか？
Otherwise, why is it called Taiwan Ten Thousand Tax?
そうでなければ、なぜ台湾万税と呼ばれるのでしょうか？
I don't think so
私はそうは思わない
However, from the tax perspective
しかし、税金の観点から見ると、
Taiwan tax is very low
台湾の税金はとても安い
you were just the first in front of us
あなたは私たちの前に最初にいただけです
From the point of view of tax ratio, the previous
税率の観点から見ると、前回は
Suppose that in your capital
あなたの首都では
Suppose you didn't do it last time
前回はやっていなかったとします
with Ossie
オッシーと
If you look at the single sale, it can reach forty
1 件の売上を見てみると、40 件に達することもあります
Swedish words are more than fifty
スウェーデン語の単語は50以上あります
more than fifty
50以上
In other words, out of a hundred dollars
つまり、100ドルのうち、
Only high taxes are taken away
取られるのは高い税金だけ
but that is to say
しかし、それはつまり
Maybe I now people want to have one
たぶん私は今、人々がそれを持ちたいと思っています
It's like he thinks it's good
彼はそれが良いと思っているようだ
feel good
いい感じ
The silver merchants are also probably their service is also very good
シルバー商人もおそらくサービスがとても良いでしょう
I'm talking about the tax value
私は税額について話しているのです
Or everyone has a consensus like this
あるいはみんながこんなふうにコンセンサスを持っている
But Taiwan's biggest problem now is that
しかし、台湾の今の最大の問題は、
If you want to pay him more taxes
彼にもっと税金を払いたいなら
not easy
不太容易
He will also first say that you show your efficiency
彼はまた、あなたが効率的であることを示していると最初に言います
I remember when Chen Shui-bian first came up
陳水扁が初めて話題になったときのことを覚えています
It wasn't that there was a Chen Dinglang
陳鼎朗がいたわけではない
he had an idea
彼にはアイデアがあった
He said I must be very inefficient
彼は私がとても効率が悪いに違いないと言いました
very inefficient
非常に非効率的
He can save a lot if he comes up
彼が出てくればかなり節約できるだろう
But he came up and didn't solve anything
しかし彼は立ち上がったが何も解決しなかった
So that problem is not equal to the fuselage alone
したがって、その問題は機体だけの問題ではありません
also makes sense
それも意味がある
If you take money from others
他人から金もらったら
Of course I want to see your performance
もちろんパフォーマンスも見たいです
Now our little one pays
今、私たちの小さな子が支払います
so we don't know where to go
だからどこに行けばいいのか分からない
so i think another idea
だから私は別のアイデアを考える
It may be to try to introduce a market economy
市場経済を導入しようとしているのかもしれない
not necessarily
必ずしも
For example, to prove that all the services I provide can be sold
たとえば、私が提供するすべてのサービスが販売できることを証明するため
don't say free price
無料価格なんて言わないで
If you sell it, you probably have one to shop around for.
売っているなら、おそらく買い物できるものがあるでしょう。
don't buy you
あなたを買わないでください
isn't he now
彼は今じゃないですか
now is forcing you to come
今はあなたに来ることを強制しています
So maybe the people have to spend their money
だから人々はお金を使わなければならないのかもしれない
i understand that is to say
つまりは分かりました
Although the tax is very low
税金がとても安いのに
but what we just said
しかし、私たちが今言ったこと
Maybe not as low as I thought
思ったほど低くないかもしれない
Maybe it's all the burden of the new place
たぶんそれはすべて新しい場所の負担です
but anyway
とにかく
many people's thoughts
多くの人の思い
I only know what a lot of people think
多くの人がどう思っているかしか分からない
that is
あれは
Your government is just not efficient so not so high
あなたたちの政府は効率的ではないのでそれほど効率的ではありません
not that high
そんなに高くない
how tall is it
身長はどれくらいですか
we don't know
私たちは知りません
The efficiency of the government is of course relatively poor
もちろん政府の効率は比較的悪い
probably can imagine
おそらく想像できる
Because it has more regulations
規制が増えるから
But the idea is to say
しかし、アイデアはこう言うことです
When you want to take money from its pocket
ポケットからお金を取り出したいとき
I think the general public's thinking is that
一般の人の考え方はこうだと思います
Maybe this person takes money
もしかしたらこの人はお金をもらっているのかもしれない
will still be wasted
まだ無駄になるだろう
It's like not much help
あまり役に立たないような
as far as we know
私たちが知っている限りでは
seems to be the same product
同じ商品のようです
more than once engraved water
水を複数回彫刻する
engraved many times
何度も刻まれました
just say it many times
ただ何度も言うだけ
This is the business value tax
これが事業価値税です
like me
私のような
He would have taken more classes
彼はもっと多くのコースを受講しただろう
that should
それはそうすべきです
he is taxing part of your worth
彼はあなたの価値の一部を課税している
I don't give you a lot of supplements
サプリメントはあまり与えません
No la
いやラ
If he wants to come down and talk to the course
彼が降りてきてコースと話したいなら
he will make up
他就補
but he is divided
しかし彼は意見が分かれている
Partial class equal to this value
この値と等しい部分クラス
But overall far away
でも全体的に遠い
His tax rate is actually not high
彼の税率は実際には高くありません
And the size of the government is not high
そして政府の規模は大きくない
compared with advanced countries
先進国と比べて
And not only not high
そして高くないだけではなく
and gradually falling
そして徐々に落ちていく
so
それで
It's a special phenomenon
特殊な現象だよ
in other words
言い換えると
The size of his government is compared with that of many countries
彼の政府の規模は多くの国の政府と比較される
are very low
非常に低いです
The tax I pay is compared with many countries
私が払っている税金は多くの国と比べて
Not as high as imagined
想像ほど高くない
no double taxation
二重課税はありません
Eh
えー
I don't know what you mean by double taxation
二重課税の意味が分からない
but
しかし
Maybe not as high as I thought
思ったより高くないかも
Thanks
ありがとう
come who
誰が来てください
last introduction
最後の紹介
Hello Mr. Yang
こんにちは、ヤンさん
that is
あれは
Just now Teacher Yang mentioned that
たった今、ヤン先生がおっしゃいました。
he
他
It's the one in Taiwan
それは台湾のものです
The gap between rich and poor has widened
貧富の差が拡大した
If the portion of income tax that is being reduced today
もし今日軽減される所得税の部分が
If the income is levied in the form of consumption tax
所得に対して消費税が課税される場合
Will it lead to a wider gap between the rich and the poor?
それは富裕層と貧困層の間の格差の拡大につながるでしょうか？
Thank you, teacher
ありがとう、先生
I just said that I am not advocating a consumption tax instead of an income tax
私は所得税の代わりに消費税を主張しているわけではないと言いました。
i made no such claim
私はそのような主張はしませんでした
Because the consumption tax is only 5% now
今は消費税が5%なので
Income tax is to let us know
所得税はお知らせします
Some 40% and some 30% have
約 40% と約 30% が
So to replace it, I think this should not be feasible
したがって、それを置き換えるには、これは実現不可能であると思います
And this is far from the traditional concept
そしてこれは従来の概念とはかけ離れています
Because the conventional wisdom is that an income tax is a better tax
なぜなら、社会通念では所得税の方が優れた税金であるからです。
Consumption tax is a US tax
消費税は米国の税金です
I just want to give you an impression that
という印象を与えたいだけです
Income tax is not as good as we thought
所得税は思ったほど良くない
From the data point of view
データの観点から見ると
In terms of progress
進歩という点では
indeed there are
確かにあります
have a lot of questions
たくさんの質問があります
The temperature elimination tax may not be as bad as we thought
温度除去税は思ったほど悪くないかもしれない
it is not a regressive tax
逆進税ではありません
My reasonable thought is that it should be a proportional tax
私の合理的な考えは、比例税であるべきだということです
proportional tax
比例税
Is it possible to indirectly make up for the shortage of hand tax with the consumption tax
手税不足を消費税で間接的に補うことは可能か
it's just an idea
それは単なるアイデアです
But the fundamental idea is to say
しかし、基本的な考え方は次のとおりです。
Negotiating the tax of hands is not as good as expected
税金の交渉は期待したほどうまくいかない
So in fact the tax potential
したがって、実際には課税の可能性は
may have a whole new and different idea
まったく新しくて異なるアイデアがあるかもしれない
new and different ideas
新しくて異なるアイデア
we know that health insurance costs
私たちは健康保険に費用がかかることを知っています
it receives a lot of tax
多額の税金を受け取っている
a lot of taxes
たくさんの税金
We know what we thought
私たちは自分たちが何を考えたかを知っています
The original idea was to say
当初のアイデアはこう言うことでした
We know that the combined filing
結合申告は
Right
右
The original idea was when it was first proposed
もともとのアイデアは最初に提案されたときのものでした
The director at that time was Yang Shiliang
当時の監督は楊世良。
He argued that the total declaration
彼は、申告総額は次のように主張した。
sum declaration
合計宣言
sum declaration I felt that I was
和宣言 私はそう感じた
Not a big war like this
こんな大戦争じゃないよ
This so-called tax itself has a large share
このいわゆる税金自体が大きな割合を占めています
You are putting the responsibility of the new master, who has already paid a heavy tax
すでに重い税金を支払った新しい主人に責任を負わせることになる
You pay him again now, and pay for the combined insurance
あなたは今彼にもう一度支払い、そして合算した保険料を支払います
Think about it, you have to file taxes twice a year
考えてみてください、税金は年に2回申告しなければなりません
Pay this tax once for the general tax
この税金を一般税として 1 回支払います
Another time for health insurance will be paid again, you see how many people
今度また健康保険料が支払われます、どれだけの人がいるかわかりますか
And the tax you keep is not a good tax in the first place.
そして、あなたが保管する税金は、そもそも良い税金ではありません。
He must have defended the old pine later
彼は後に老松を守ったに違いない
I don't know how you feel about Gu Song's way of defending
ク・ソンの守り方についてどう思っているのか分からない
If I feel it myself, it seems that there is nothing special
自分で感じてみると特に何もないようですが
Every year when I declare the tax I keep, it is a very painful thing for me
毎年、納めている税金を申告するのは、私にとってとても苦痛なことです。
Because you pay a lot of taxes, you have to pay a lot of taxes
税金をたくさん払っているから、税金もたくさん払わなければならない
That would be very painful, it would be like asking you to say that
それはとても辛いですよ、そんなことを言ってるようなものです
Because the payment is equal to the largest expenditure in the whole year, that's right
一年で一番大きな出費に相当する支払いだから、そうだね
Did you say that the health insurance association, I don’t feel anything special
健康保険組合、特に何も感じないって言いましたか？
But NHS finances are doing really well now
しかし、NHSの財政は現在非常にうまくいっている
Why is it good?
なぜ良いのでしょうか？
because he received a lot of taxes
彼は多額の税金を受け取っているから
How is this tax collected?
この税金はどのように徴収されるのでしょうか?
That is, it has a wide range of tax machines
つまり、幅広い税金機械を備えています
Tax machine is very wide
納税機はとても広いです
anything is welcome
何でも歓迎です
it has a discovery
それは発見がある
It is the income that encourages customers to pay a lot of taxes
それは顧客に多額の税金を支払うよう促す収入です
Such a small sword board would have been based on the new hand
このような小さな剣板は新しい手を基にしたものであろう
its for new hands
新しい手に向けたものです
A tax on re-customers other than hands
ハンド以外の再顧客に対する税金
other than novice
初心者以外の
For example, to encourage
たとえば、励ますために
it receives a lot of tax
多額の税金を受け取っている
another one
もう一つ
it has another major discovery what is
もう一つ大きな発見があります
The major discovery is that
大きな発見は、
Taiwan is under the original health care system
台湾には独自の医療制度がある
The ones held by new hands are much lower
新しい手に握られたものははるかに低い
much lower
はるかに低いです
So it then says
それで、それはこう言います
the part that doesn't hug you
あなたを抱きしめない部分
I will pay you an extra tax now
今すぐ追加の税金を支払います
it saw a huge increase in revenue
収益が大幅に増加しました
So now health insurance
それで今は健康保険
it is financially
それは経済的にです
look what happened not long ago
見てください、少し前に何が起こったのか
Are you hugging someone and saying that your finances are bad?
誰かを抱きしめながら、あなたの経済状況が悪いと言っていますか？
good income now
今では良い収入がある
right
右
arrive
到着
Take a little from middle, take a little from C, I will engrave two pieces for you for 100 yuan
真ん中から少し取って、Cから少し取って、100元で2個彫刻します
do you feel it
あなたはそれを感じていますか
may not feel much
あまり感じないかもしれない
It is a little bit eastward, but it has a lot of taxes
少し東にありますが税金が多いです
Very wide, you see, everyone in Taiwan only needs to pay one yuan
とても広いですね、台湾の人はみんな1元払えばいいだけです
What can you earn?
何が得られますか?
More than 20 million
2000万以上
Because there are 23 million people
2300万人もいるから
You have to pay a dime, everyone pays a dime
あなたは10セントを支払わなければなりません、誰もが10セントを支払います
You have an income of more than 20 million
収入が2000万以上あるのに
Think about it, if you pay 100 yuan to 100 yuan per person
考えてみてください、1人あたり100元対100元を支払った場合
So its tax is very wide, very wide
したがって、その税金は非常に広範囲にわたります、非常に広範囲です
It draws a big circle, which is completely different from what it thinks is loud
うるさいと思っているのとは全然違う大きな円を描く
When it actually does, it doesn't complain now
実際にそうなったとしても、今は文句を言わない
it says my taxes are fine
私の税金は大丈夫だそうです
It says finances are getting cheap money
財政は安いお金を手に入れていると言う
So that system, I think we might know
それでそのシステム、私たちは知っているかもしれないと思います
There is a very important principle when collecting taxes
税金を徴収する際には非常に重要な原則があります
I hope it's forehead hair will be the same so that it won't feel pain
額の毛も同じになって痛くならないように
like i said every year when the role, i'm in pain
毎年この役の時に言ってるけど、私は痛いんだ
Did you pluck too much forehead hair that time?
あの時額の毛を抜きすぎたんですか？
I feel very uncomfortable
とても不快に感じます
i'm there every day
私は毎日そこにいます
my feet are so broken
私の足はとても壊れています
Especially considering that many people
特に人が多いことを考えると、
hands earn more money than me
手は私よりもお金を稼いでいます
Broken feet, less than me, etc.
足が壊れている、私よりも小さいなど。
very upset
とても動揺している
But at the health insurance meeting
しかし、健康保険の会議では
I believe you all feel nothing
皆さんは何も感じていないと思います
because he buckles
彼は座るから
come here for a smoke
タバコを吸いにここに来てください
carve a little there
そこに少し彫ってください
But he has a lot of taxes
しかし彼は多額の税金を持っている
tax is very wide
税金の範囲は非常に広い
like i said
私が言ったように
23 million people
2,300万人
Only one foot per person
お一人様片足のみ
just one dollar
たった1ドル
right
右
He collected a bunch
彼はたくさん集めた
tantamount to tax design
税金の設計に等しい
I think to think very differently
とても違うと思います
Professor Yang Hello, Mr. Yang
ヤン先生、ヤン先生、こんにちは。
i want to ask two questions
2つの質問がしたいです
that is
あれは
Professor Yang just mentioned
ヤン教授が先ほど言及した
part of the lock tax
ロック税の一部
The country's locked tax areas are divided into
この国の固定課税地域は次のように分かれています。
Lock in the tax payment period during the silver interest period
銀の利息期間中の納税期間を固定する
Personal comprehensive lock-in tax
個人総合ロックイン税
That
それか
Professor Yang here is mainly for
ここのヤン教授の主な目的は、
Personal comprehensive lock-in tax
個人総合ロックイン税では
real class lock
実クラスロック
One of the new locks
新しいロックの 1 つ
Does it mean that this new lock is
この新しいロックは
Why compared with the consumption tax
なぜ消費税と比較するのか
If this is compared with consumption tax
これを消費税に例えると
relatively representative
比較的代表的な
The second question is
2番目の質問は、
In the past, our country focused on the income tax
かつて我が国は所得税を中心に考えてきました。
That's when the minimum tax was introduced
そこで最低限度の課税が導入されたのです
What about the minimum tax system
課税最低限制度はどうなるのか
As Professor Yang said
楊先生のおっしゃる通り
It's just that he's not included in the property tax.
ただ、固定資産税には含まれていないということです。
It's the property
それは財産です
If it is included in the property
物件に含まれている場合
to the minimum tax system
最低限度の課税制度へ
will that follow
それは続きますか
because i'm not partisan
私は党派ではないので
I wonder if that will affect the vote
それが投票に影響するのか気になる
You want to take money from the people
国民から金を巻き上げたいのか
I don't think that's a big deal for everyone.
それは誰にとっても大したことではないと思います。
Moreover, there is a county in Taiwan that says that it often increases the price
また、台湾には頻繁に値上げをするという県があります。
not only not from you
それはあなたから出たものではないだけでなく、
He also lowered your taxes
彼は税金も下げた
give you a lot of benefits
あなたにたくさんの恩恵を与えます
No, you want to say that every year when the election
いや、毎年選挙の時に言いたいんだろうね
The old man is overweight today
今日の老人は太りすぎです
Because, for example, the U.S. dollar factory overweight
なぜなら、例えば、米ドル工場はオーバーウェイトだからです。
The KMT will continue to increase
国民党は今後も勢力を拡大していく
but take money from you
でもあなたからお金を取る
I think ordinary politicians don't dare to speak.
普通の政治家はあえて発言しないと思います。
not quite dare
あまり勇気がありません
So what you said earlier
それで、先ほどあなたが言ったことは、
I don't think so
私はそうは思わない
My point just says
私の言いたいことはただ言います
RSS
RSS
what we just compared
今比較したもの
For example, compared with European and American countries
例えば欧米諸国と比べて
Like the United States, probably
おそらくアメリカと同じように、
The new system of the first Russia probably accounted for 60
最初のロシアの新しいシステムはおそらく60を占めた
About 56. more
約56.もっと見る
Other capitals are about 48
他の首都は約48
in other words
言い換えると
The European Xi Jinping Country in Europe
欧州における欧州の習近平国家
But Taiwan's words accounted for 75
しかし台湾の発言は75を占めた
means
意味
from a certain point of view
ある観点から見ると
It means that other capitals have not grasped
他の資本が把握していないことを意味します
Because of the words you have mastered in other countries
他国で習得した言葉のせいで
The new system of the first Russia will not account for so high
最初のロシアの新しいシステムはそれほど高いものではないでしょう
Because Taiwan accounts for 75%
台湾が75％を占めているので
even quite high
かなり高い場合でも
Compared with the data of those countries
それらの国のデータと比較すると
high
高
means equal to other Russian
他のロシア語と同等という意味
not mastered well
うまくマスターできていない
That makes you a new system of the first Russia
それはあなたを最初のロシアの新しいシステムにします
75% of your tax return
納税申告書の 75%
so
それで
Didn't say what happened to other capitals
他の首都がどうなったかについては言及しなかった
i just say
私はちょうど言います
General impression of Taiwan
台湾の一般的な印象
The general impression is that
一般的な印象としては、
Taiwan's personal broken hands seem to be broken minds
台湾の個人的な壊れた手は壊れた心のようだ
From the data point of view, this concept
データの観点から見ると、この概念は
not necessarily completely wrong
必ずしも完全に間違っているわけではない
Because compared to other countries
他国に比べてだから
It is indeed flat
確かに平らですね
Ye Ping Gao
イェ・ピン・ガオ
Master Yang Liao
ヤン・リャオ先生
I
私
When Taiwan was broken, there was a lot of loss
台湾が崩壊したとき、多くの損失があった
Simplest central government
最も単純な中央政府
What about that water bottle?
その水筒はどうですか？
Inheritance tax, what kind of property tax can be lowered for him
相続税、どのような固定資産税を軽減できるのか
Did you talk about the Japanese one at that time?
その時、日本のことについて話しましたか？
say clothing
服と言う
In fact, Taiwan also has
実は台湾にもあるんです
Taiwan also has
台湾にもあります
I worked in a trading company before retiring from a trading company
商社に勤めていましたが、商社を退職しました。
all of that Taiwan
台湾のすべて
to what extent do you capitalize me
あなたは私をどの程度利用しますか
he has the tax office
彼は税務署を持っています
So he has the thermostat tube
それで彼はサーモスタットチューブを持っています
Just the latest newspaper, etc.
最新の新聞など。
He gave me a pipe for the police
彼は私に警察にパイプをくれた
But the clothes are very busy
でも洋服はとても忙しいです
He usually doesn't come just to check taxes
彼は通常、税金を確認するためだけに来るわけではありません
Honglian was puzzled when he came
ホンリアンは彼が来たとき当惑した
I'll check it out, Honglian will only come during the holidays
チェックしてみます、Honglian は休暇中にしか来ません
He was not happy during the investigation
彼は捜査中に満足していなかった
We have rules, you
私たちにはルールがあります、あなた
All the corner tax certificates are related to our car
コーナーの納税証明書はすべて私たちの車に関連しています
What about taxation, he helps beauties want to save Qilian
税金についてはどうですか、彼は祁連を救いたいと願う美女たちを助けます
Then you are now in the 103rd year of the Republic of China
さて、あなたは今、中華民国103年目に入りました。
He can say sorry
彼はごめんなさいと言える
We have a problem with your 98 year old one
あなたの98歳のお年寄りには問題があります
From July 31st to October 31st in 1998
1998年7月31日から10月31日まで
Where can you show me? The company will hire two floats
どこを案内できますか?会社はフロートを 2 台雇います
Then go to the state-owned machinery, because our company's
それから国有の機械に行きます、なぜなら私たちの会社は
The business volume is 2 billion US dollars, let's go there
取引額は20億ドル、そこに行きましょう
OK OK OK so yes that's another point this
OK、OK、はい、それがもう一つのポイントです
Because Taiwan is encouraging others, for example
なぜなら、台湾は他の国を励ましているからです。
There is a joke that you just pick up the business card like someone else
他人のように名刺を拾うという冗談があります
Three times out of ten, Zhang said the chairman or general manager
張氏は10回に3回、会長かゼネラルマネージャーがそう言った。
I have many friends who are doing this trade
この商売をしている友人がたくさんいます
Others can also apply for this trade
他の人もこの取引に応募できます
Maoyu license, there are really regulations
まおゆうライセンス、本当に規制があるんですね
Your cat feather license company gives you
猫の羽のライセンス会社があなたに提供するのは、
If you have no business activities within three years, it will be canceled
3年以内に営業活動が無い場合は解除となります
but i really can't find a business what to do
でも本当にビジネスが見つからない、どうしよう
I don't want to log out
ログアウトしたくない
Because there are many advantages to not having to log out.
ログアウトする必要がないことには多くの利点があるためです。
like the one in my kids house now
今私の子供の家にあるもののように
interior designer
インテリアデザイナー
he has a license
彼は免許を持っています
His motorcycle family can reimburse
彼のオートバイの家族は払い戻すことができます
Is 40,000 a treat?
4万はご褒美ですか？
Is it possible to report on business behavior?
ビジネス行動について報告することは可能ですか?
Report that execution?
その処刑を報告しますか？
then my own motorcycle
それから自分のバイク
I'm going to do my best
全力で頑張ります
My car owner wants to refuel himself
私の車の所有者は自分で燃料を補給したいと考えています
this is unfair
これは不公平だ
So it shouldn't let you discount it
だからそれを値引きさせるべきではない
then what should we do
じゃあどうすればいいのか
just looking for friends
ただ友達を探しているだけ
yours
あなたのもの
expanded to
に拡張されました
Even if the days come, the photos will not be lost
たとえその日が来ても 写真は失われない
Just use my name to ship
私の名前を使って発送してください
yes
はい
So this kind of encouragement
ですから、このような励ましは
unfair tax system
不公平税制
yes
はい
So your tax system
つまり、あなたの税制は
say you are in hong kong
あなたは香港にいると言ってください
In particular, there are many correct ways to set it up
特に、正しい設定方法がたくさんあります
But just like this, the east factory and the west factory are all empty
でもこのままでは東工場も西工場も空いてしまいました
Because it should be said that the reform of the sky should be more important than the reform of words
言葉の改革よりも空の改革が大事だと言うべきだから
yes
はい
Thanks
ありがとう
As you mentioned, it means that everyone should know each other in terms of academic qualifications.
先ほどもおっしゃいましたように、学歴的にはみんながお互いを知っているということです。
In fact, a Policy cannot be decoupled from its implementation
実際、ポリシーをその実装から切り離すことはできません。
You can't say I only talk about one Policy
私が 1 つのポリシーについてのみ話しているとは言えません
but did not talk about an implementation issue
しかし実装の問題については話さなかった
For example, I just talked about a tax matter
たとえば、先ほど税金の話をしましたが、
when i just listened to him
ちょうど彼の話を聞いたとき
I feel good listening to my classmate
クラスメイトの話を聞いていて気持ちがいい
but what you just said
でもあなたが今言ったこと
Whether the tax affairs are good or not will lead to other issues
税務が良いかどうかは別の問題につながる
for example
例えば
So it is equivalent to a lot of times, it is a policy
なので多くの回に相当するのがポリシーです
when implementing a policy
政策を実行するとき
Can't be decoupled from your executive plane
エグゼクティブプレーンから切り離すことはできません
It performs very inefficiently
パフォーマンスが非常に非効率的です
For example, the boss of your company
たとえば、あなたの会社の上司が
It stipulates that you can't buy a car for more than 2 million
200万以上の車は買えないという規定がある
Suppose you exceed 2 million
200万を超えたとします
He will ratify you to 2 million
彼はあなたを200万人に承認しました
But the 2 million will be included in that asset
ただし、200 万はその資産に含まれます
In the list of sales assets
販売資産一覧へ
He has a rule of forty percent
彼には40パーセントというルールがある
So if our car exceeds 2 million
つまり、私たちの車が200万を超えたら
forty percent
40パーセント
800,000 in me
私の中に80万
I can pay taxes this year
今年も納税できます
Then I will divide it into 10 years
それを10年に分けてみます
Everyone can take lessons
誰でもレッスンが受けられます
but we didn't
でも私たちはしませんでした
If there is no such thing as a job, there is no salary
仕事が無ければ給料も無い
I bought that Yirong Zheqi 800,000
私はそのYrong Zheqi 800,000を購入しました
i don't have a dime
私は一銭も持っていない
he pays for himself
彼は自分で支払います
So this implementation aspect is really
したがって、この実装の側面は実際には
It's more important than you to reform a little bit
少し改革することの方が大切です
a friend of mine just said
私の友人がちょうど言いました
sometimes taiwan
時々台湾
The best day in Taiwan is to say
台湾で最高の日はこう言う
start your own company
自分の会社を始める
It's big to report to work after eating
食べてから仕事に報告するのは大きいです
Reporting a job is a big deal
仕事の報告は大事なことです
He said that this day in Taiwan
彼はこの日台湾でこう言った。
will have a good time
楽しい時間を過ごします
Of course he has rules
もちろん彼にはルールがある
you this
あなたはこれ
look at him
彼を見て
do you sometimes guess one
時々推測しますか
I talked about
について話しました
i think in general
一般的には思います
If we look at the system in terms of money received
受け取ったお金の観点からシステムを見ると
of course
もちろん
The second-generation health insurance supplementary insurance fee is a lot of money
第二世代健康保険の付加保険料は高額です
But he actually received the most
しかし、実際に最も多くのものを受け取ったのは彼でした
Not the non-earn income part
不労所得部分ではない
It's already paid for this
しかし、これはすでに支払われています
This part of the so-called seller income
いわゆる売主収入のこの部分
because he has this
彼はこれを持っているから
In particular there is an insured salary scale
特に保険付き給与表があります
The upper limit of the grading table is more than 180,000
グレーディングテーブルの上限は180,000以上
no class at all
授業がまったくない
what about this part
この部分はどうですか
you don't have class
あなたには授業がありません
but your boss wants to pay for you
でもあなたの上司はあなたに給料を払いたがっている
so this part
それでこの部分
let's just say
言ってみよう
That's 300,000 a month
月30万ですよ
Then you have 120,000 of this money
そうすればあなたはこのお金のうち120,000を持っています
yourself
あなた自身
did not pay insurance premiums
保険料を支払わなかった
But the boss wants to help you pay this money every month
でも上司はあなたがこのお金を毎月支払うのを手伝いたいと思っています
this money adds up
このお金は合計されます
The second-generation health insurance supplementary premium was overcharged by 400
第二世代健康保険付加保険料が400円過剰請求されました
Probably received 43 billion
おそらく430億受け取った
just this part
この部分だけ
The boss has more than 20 billion talents
ボスは200億以上の才能を持っている
In fact, the money that encouragement actually accounts for is not much.
実際のところ、励ましに実際に費やされる金額はそれほど多くありません。
for encouraging him to have another
彼にもう一つ食べるよう勧めてくれて
Everyone would know if they knew
知ってれば誰でも分かるだろう
5000 yuan
5000元
That is, there is no class below 5,000 yuan.
つまり、5,000元以下のクラスはありません。
So now a lot of interest is splitting bills
今、多くの関心が割り勘にあります
Disassembled to say less than 5,000 yuan
分解すると5000元以下
So now we need to amend the law
だから今こそ法律を改正する必要がある
It is the annual settlement
毎年恒例の決算です
that is
あれは
avoid this part
この部分を避ける
because too smart
賢すぎるから
everyone is evading taxes
みんな脱税してる
We always blame the government
私たちはいつも政府を非難します
But we are smart enough to say
しかし、私たちはこう言うことができるほど賢いのです
we will follow
私たちはフォローします
this government
この政府
He's pretending like we're here to play this
彼はまるで私たちがこれをするためにここに来たかのようなふりをしている
game
ゲーム
So actually
それで実際には
talking about the whole system
システム全体について話す
I just came to a conclusion that I think is very good
とても良いと思う結論に達しました
that is
あれは
ideal or
理想か、
system
制度
But this executive level
しかし、この幹部レベルは
if with some twist
何らかの工夫があれば
It's not just that it can't hit the target
標的に当てられないだけではない
And it will greatly discount this fairness
そしてそれはこの公平性を大幅に損なうことになる
that's all
以上
then you check me to find out what's there
それから、そこに何があるのか​​調べるために私をチェックしてください
that is
あれは
It was said in the news before
前にニュースで言ってた
The rich in France are just dissatisfied with the way France treats them
フランスの富裕層はフランスの自分たちの扱いに不満を抱いているだけだ
The heavier income tax or other taxes
所得税やその他の税金が重くなる
So I immigrated to Singapore directly.
それでシンガポールに直接移住しました。
If our taxes are getting fairer
私たちの税金がもっと公平になったら
But our powerful entrepreneurs
しかし、私たちの強力な起業家たちは、
or have the strength to create
または創造する力を持っています
If the high-level people run away
偉い人が逃げたら
Isn't it bad for our country?
それは我が国にとって悪いことではないでしょうか？
of course it is
もちろん
So that means
つまり、
like us people
私たち人間のように
That's the way to say it.
そういう言い方ですね。
It's not so easy for you to tax him
あなたにとって彼に課税するのはそれほど簡単ではありません
From a theoretical point of view
理論的な観点から
That is to say, from the point of view of efficiency
つまり、効率の観点から言えば、
That is to say, for those incomes with relatively high liquidity
つまり、比較的流動性の高い収入の場合
The tax rate would have been lower
税率はもっと低かっただろう
From the point of view of efficiency
効率の観点から見ると
less efficient
効率が低い
So overall
全体的に見て
like i said taiwan has some structural problems
私が言ったように、台湾にはいくつかの構造的問題がある
You have a lot of companies in China
中国にはたくさんの会社があります
Then teach the rich man
それから金持ちに教えてください
So it's not as easy as we imagined
だからそれは私たちが想像していたほど簡単ではない
It's not that we have to deal with those language people
私たちがそれらの言語を話す人々と取引しなければならないというわけではありません
We say positive education income you don't pay taxes
税金を支払っていない場合、プラスの教育収入があると言われます
so i will tax you
だからあなたに税金を課します
This is theoretically more fair and just
これは理論的にはより公平で公正です
Because you have income, you don't have to pay taxes
すでに収入があるので税金を払う必要がない
but when actually doing
しかし実際にやってみると
not as easy as we imagined
私たちが想像していたほど簡単ではありません
Look at the tax reduction in our text last time
前回の本文で減税について見てみましょう
But the economy as a whole has also become worse
しかし経済全体も悪化している
So this means
つまり、これは意味します
This is a structural problem
これは構造的な問題です
It's not that you're rich
あなたが金持ちだというわけではありません
So you sleep with heavier feet
だから足が重くなって寝ることになる
not so simple
そんなに単純ではない
may have a whole new and different idea
まったく新しくて異なるアイデアがあるかもしれない
new and different ideas
新しくて異なるアイデア
structural issues like these
このような構造的な問題
How about a new idea for you
新しいアイデアはいかがですか
New idea to engrave this problem
この問題を解決する新しいアイデア
instead of just saying how about fairness and justice
公平性や正義はどうかと言うだけではなく
like you just said
あなたが今言ったように
These people run away when you're there
あなたがそこにいると、この人たちは逃げ出す
Not good for Taiwan market
台湾市場には不向き
It's like losing both
両方失ったようなものだ
so this should
これはそうすべきです
really want one
本当に欲しい
It was a whole new and different idea
それは全く新しい、異なるアイデアでした
come to ask a question
質問しに来てください
That is to say, just at the beginning
つまり、最初だけ
A school of economics in the United States is
アメリカの経済学部は、
he thinks
彼が考えている
He said the most drastic way is to say
彼は、最も抜本的な方法はこう言うことだと言いました。
Tax that should be expected with consumption tax
消費税とともに期待されるべき税金
And if I remember correctly
そして私の記憶が正しければ
Asked whether the director was with me at the time
その時監督は私と一緒にいたかどうか尋ねられた
He said that Hong Kong seemed to be in a certain period
彼は香港がある時期にあるようだと言いました
very short period
非常に短い期間
implemented this method
このメソッドを実装しました
Of course, because there are so many objections to legal persons
もちろん、法人に対する反対意見が非常に多いため、
There is no Xi Jinping who said to change his father's explanation
父親の説明を変えると言う習近平は存在しない
So I'm going to ask two questions
そこで2つ質問させていただきます
I don't know, subsidy chief, you don't have subsidy at this time.
わかりません、補助金局長、今補助金はありませんよ。
No
いいえ
You subsidize first because I'm going to talk and I'm coming to an end
私が話して終わりに近づいているので、あなたが最初に補助してください
to finish
終わる
I think because of the change in the last year
昨年の変化のせいだと思う
Actually on this question
実はこの質問に関しては
Discuss with each other many times
お互いに何度も話し合う
I don't think there's a definitive answer to this
これに対する決定的な答えはないと思います
But we also recite many times
でも私たちも何度も唱えます
I think this consumption tax is in Taiwan
この消費税は台湾にあると思います
With Yang Jiahong, we are on the low side
ヤン・ジアホンの場合、私たちは劣勢にあります
improve this direction
この方向性を改善する
yes but
はい、でも
For some scholars, it is hoped that
一部の学者にとっては、次のことを期待しています。
consumption tax can be substituted for all
全て消費税で代用可能です
So this is controversial
だからこれは物議を醸している
And with reservations
そして予約制で
No country in the world does this
世界中でこんなことをする国はない
Then I want to follow the direction of Yang Jiahong
それなら私は楊家紅の指示に従いたいと思います
all right but
大丈夫、でも
When designing this tax system, many
この税制を設計する際には、多くの
has his first challenge
初めての挑戦をする
For example, when he was working, the concept of lifetime income and consumption
例えば、現役時代は生涯所得と消費という概念があった。
It is perfectly feasible in a closed economic system
閉鎖的な経済システムでは完全に実現可能です
But as he just said
しかし、彼が今言ったように、
The broken locks are also difficult to grow
壊れた錠前も成長しにくい
I believe GST is also somewhat difficult to sleep on
GSTも若干寝にくいと思います
Why
なぜ
A Taiwanese is a small open geographic system
台湾人は小さく開かれた地理体系です
what i just said
私が今言ったこと
My family eats, drinks and has fun abroad
私の家族は海外で食べたり飲んだり楽しんでいます
May I ask how can I go to the class to pay the GST?
GSTを取得するにはどうすればクラスに通えるか聞いてもいいですか？
So this part is actually not conclusive
したがって、この部分は実際には決定的なものではありません
But basically Taiwan's consumption tax
でも基本的には台湾の消費税
the lowest in the world
世界で一番低い
So we ended up saying that we can slightly increase the
したがって、最終的には、
But you make up some of the tax deficit
しかし、税金不足の一部を補てんするのはあなたです
but to completely replace
しかし完全に置き換えるには
we are law abiding
私たちは法を遵守します
Thanks
ありがとう
we're going to ask a very simple question
とても簡単な質問をします
that is
あれは
Because we can't read the whole proposal to change
変更提案全体を読むことができないため
I have the impression that this idea also appeared in our report
この考え方は報告書にも出てきたような気がします
yes
はい
Has it attracted the attention of any fiscal and taxation unit?
それは財政および税務部門の注目を集めましたか
Indonesia knows
インドネシアは知っている
From what I understand now, this shouldn't be the point
私が今理解しているところによると、これは重要なことではありません
now is not the point
今は問題ではない
Now the Ministry of Finance is real estate
今、財務省は不動産です
he is a focus now
彼は今注目の的です
But it's like raising the tax
でも増税みたいなもんだよ
I think the general public is against it
一般人は反対だと思う
Therefore, the main reason is that it is generally recognized that
したがって、主な理由は、一般に次のように認識されているためです。
GST is a split tax
GST は分割税です
so you see
ご覧のように
like in five percent executive yuan
5％の行政人民元のように
He can skip the legislature
彼は議会をスキップできる
He can directly increase to 7
彼は直接 7 まで増やすことができます
Because of the rules he can turn it up to 10
ルールのせいで彼はそれを10まで上げることができる
But he was not moved at all
しかし彼は全く動かなかった
why not touched at all
なぜ全く触れないのか
It's obviously not an easy thing to do
それは明らかに簡単なことではありません
not easy thing
簡単なことではありません
Because it is generally believed that the consumption tax is a split tax
消費税は分割税であると一般的に考えられているため
disadvantageous to the poor
貧乏人に不利な
as long as you are one
あなたが一人である限り
or
また
Right now it means he's turning it up by 5 to 10
現時点では、彼はそれを5から10まで上げていることを意味します
He doesn't have to go through the legislature
彼は議会を通過する必要はない
but he was not moved
しかし彼は動かなかった
not moved
不感動
He is not even moved by 5 to 6
彼は5、6でも動じない
It means that if the tax is raised, it will be very loud.
増税すると非常にうるさくなるということです。
And when you turn it up, think about it
そしてそれを上げたら、それについて考えてください
I imagine the prices will be raised as well.
価格も値上げされると思います。
The whole will also be raised
全体も上がります
Because this increase is a bit similar to the preferential price of water and electricity.
なぜなら、この値上げは水道や電気の優遇価格に少し似ているからです。
turn this up
これを上げる
So this is tuned up
それでこれは調整されています
Like Japan, hasn't he recently raised his voice?
日本同様、最近声を上げていませんか？
is good in the short run
短期的には良い
he has a big problem
彼には大きな問題がある
Long term is of course more difficult to say
もちろん長期的なことを言うのはさらに難しい
is good in the short term
短期的には良い
And what he said at the time
そしてその時彼が言ったこと
is through how big a
どれくらい大きなものですか
tantamount to the opposition
野党と同じ
Democratic Party
民主党
agree with the ruling party
与党に同意する
The ruling party later stepped down
その後与党は辞任した
equal to somewhat equal to
等しい ある程度等しい
The ruling party was then
当時の与党は
Promise to do this
これを行うと約束してください
that cost a lot
それは多額の費用がかかる
This price means
この価格の意味は、
If you turn it up, I'll let you step down
上げてくれたら降ろさせてあげるよ
this has to pay
これは支払わなければなりません
But Japan is a bit forced
でも日本はちょっと強引だね
has come to a point where it doesn't
そうならないところまで来ている
far from enough
十分とは程遠い
have to
した方が良い
but he is also
しかし彼もまた
was one equal to one
1は1に等しい
It means that at that time the Prime Minister already had a
ということは、その時点ですでに首相は
It's like having a jig dance
ジグダンスをしているようなものです
Just improve this and I probably won't be selected.
これを改善するだけではおそらく選ばれないでしょう。
that result
その結果
So the Prime Minister at that time did what he did, I think it was the same.
ですから、当時の総理もやったことは同じだったと思います。
is also full
もいっぱいです
fruitful
実り豊かな
you see Taiwan now you see
台湾が見えてきましたね
You don't have to tune up by force show
無理にショーを調整する必要はありません
everyone dare not come
みんなあえて来ないでね
because you turn up the words
あなたが言葉を上げてしまうから
This will be with water
これは水と一緒になります
turn up the same
同じように現れる
This is bound to have serious consequences
これは間違いなく深刻な結果をもたらすだろう
so everyone
だからみんな
dare not do
あえてやらない
So what I thought of was
そこで私が考えたのは、
There may be a way is
方法があるかも知れませんが、
Will raising this will lower the tax for new makers?
これを引き上げると新規メーカーの税金が安くなるでしょうか？
there is one
ここに一つ
Having an equal is having an advantage like this
対等であることにはこのような利点があります
Turn it up here
ここで上げてください
But the new samurai tax brought it down like this
しかし、新しい武士税はこのように引き下げました
Put it all together
すべてをまとめて
Perhaps the public may be more aware
もしかしたら一般の人ももっと認知しているかもしれない
You only want to raise this, I think this
あなたはこれだけを上げたいのだと思います
I probably don't have it easy
おそらく楽ではないでしょう
not feasible these days
最近では実現不可能
not feasible
現実的ではありません
our time is almost up
私たちの時間はもう終わりです
US tax is a very difficult problem
私たちの税金は非常に難しい問題です
There are many problems with this tax in Taiwan
台湾のこの税金には多くの問題があります
very low on the one hand
一方で非常に低い
because I study history
歴史を勉強しているので
The ratio of our current tax ratio
現在の税率の比率は次のとおりです。
tomorrow
明日
Even lower than in the Qing Dynasty
清朝よりもさらに低い
so it's a big problem
それは大きな問題です
But on the one hand, there are many people who do not pay taxes
しかしその一方で、税金を支払わない人もたくさんいます。
On the other hand, the country has no money to spend
一方、国には使えるお金がない
Every year, as Teacher Yang said
ヤン先生が言っていたように、毎年
Two to three hundred billion less
2～3千億少ない
Of course the one just mentioned
もちろん今挙げたものは
The government randomly lowered it by two or three hundred billion
政府はそれをランダムに2000億か3000億引き下げた
These questions are very
これらの質問は非常に
And the treaty is very difficult
そしてこの条約は非常に難しいものです
So what about today, Professor Yang will give us a detailed explanation from the beginning
さて今日は楊教授が最初から詳しく解説します
give us a very clear explanation
非常に明確な説明をしてください
very good speech
とても良いスピーチ
thank him thank you
彼に感謝します、ありがとう